[{"id":"Q1","note":"Open-ended responses are reported as coded.","question":" What do you think are the three most important problems facing Austin today?","answers":[{"text":"Traffic/ Roads/ Transportation","total":0.82,"yrs05":0.85,"yrs620":0.85,"yrs21":0.79,"livCou":0.83,"livAus":0.82,"livCen":0.79,"age18":0.78,"age35":0.85},{"text":"Affordability/ Cost of Living/ Affordable Housing/ Gentrification","total":0.5,"yrs05":0.43,"yrs620":0.51,"yrs21":0.52,"livCou":0.44,"livAus":0.56,"livCen":0.59,"age18":0.45,"age35":0.53},{"text":"Population Growth","total":0.24,"yrs05":0.24,"yrs620":0.22,"yrs21":0.25,"livCou":0.25,"livAus":0.23,"livCen":0.2,"age18":0.26,"age35":0.23},{"text":"Jobs/ Wages/ Unemployment/ Poverty/ Homelessness","total":0.17,"yrs05":0.18,"yrs620":0.13,"yrs21":0.18,"livCou":0.14,"livAus":0.2,"livCen":0.21,"age18":0.23,"age35":0.14},{"text":"Education","total":0.12,"yrs05":0.1,"yrs620":0.14,"yrs21":0.12,"livCou":0.11,"livAus":0.13,"livCen":0.12,"age18":0.15,"age35":0.11},{"text":"Water/Drought","total":0.11,"yrs05":0.11,"yrs620":0.14,"yrs21":0.08,"livCou":0.1,"livAus":0.11,"livCen":0.09,"age18":0.06,"age35":0.13},{"text":"Crime","total":0.1,"yrs05":0.1,"yrs620":0.08,"yrs21":0.11,"livCou":0.12,"livAus":0.08,"livCen":0.06,"age18":0.1,"age35":0.1},{"text":"None of these","total":0.05,"yrs05":0.06,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.06,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0.04,"livCen":0.04,"age18":0.07,"age35":0.04}]},{"id":"Q2","note":null,"question":"Do you think Austin is...","answers":[{"text":"Doing a good job of remaining unique from other major U.S. cities","total":0.38,"yrs05":0.5,"yrs620":0.35,"yrs21":0.35,"livCou":0.37,"livAus":0.4,"livCen":0.4,"age18":0.5,"age35":0.32},{"text":"Unique but becoming more similar to other major U.S. cities","total":0.49,"yrs05":0.44,"yrs620":0.51,"yrs21":0.5,"livCou":0.46,"livAus":0.52,"livCen":0.55,"age18":0.44,"age35":0.51},{"text":"Similar to other major U.S. cities","total":0.13,"yrs05":0.06,"yrs620":0.14,"yrs21":0.15,"livCou":0.18,"livAus":0.08,"livCen":0.06,"age18":0.06,"age35":0.17}]},{"id":"Q3","note":null,"question":"Do you believe Austin is at risk of losing its appeal because of the rising cost of living?","answers":[{"text":"Yes, definitely","total":0.54,"yrs05":0.41,"yrs620":0.53,"yrs21":0.59,"livCou":0.53,"livAus":0.54,"livCen":0.55,"age18":0.47,"age35":0.57},{"text":"Yes, somewhat","total":0.32,"yrs05":0.34,"yrs620":0.34,"yrs21":0.3,"livCou":0.3,"livAus":0.35,"livCen":0.35,"age18":0.38,"age35":0.29},{"text":"Not really","total":0.11,"yrs05":0.2,"yrs620":0.12,"yrs21":0.07,"livCou":0.13,"livAus":0.09,"livCen":0.09,"age18":0.11,"age35":0.11},{"text":"Definitely not","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Unsure","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.01}]},{"id":"Q4","note":null,"question":"Has the rising cost of living in Austin limited how much of your earnings you've been able to put into personal savings?","answers":[{"text":"Yes","total":0.66,"yrs05":0.67,"yrs620":0.6,"yrs21":0.69,"livCou":0.59,"livAus":0.72,"livCen":0.7,"age18":0.76,"age35":0.6},{"text":"No","total":0.19,"yrs05":0.16,"yrs620":0.25,"yrs21":0.17,"livCou":0.2,"livAus":0.19,"livCen":0.21,"age18":0.1,"age35":0.24},{"text":"Unsure","total":0.05,"yrs05":0.07,"yrs620":0.06,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0.05,"livCen":0.04,"age18":0.05,"age35":0.05},{"text":"Prefer not to answer","total":0,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0,"livCou":0,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0,"age18":0,"age35":0.01},{"text":"Not applicable to me","total":0.09,"yrs05":0.1,"yrs620":0.09,"yrs21":0.09,"livCou":0.15,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.06,"age18":0.08,"age35":0.1}]},{"id":"Q5","note":null,"question":"Has your neighborhood experienced gentrification?","answers":[{"text":"Yes","total":0.29,"yrs05":0.32,"yrs620":0.24,"yrs21":0.31,"livCou":0.17,"livAus":0.41,"livCen":0.58,"age18":0.42,"age35":0.22},{"text":"No","total":0.62,"yrs05":0.52,"yrs620":0.7,"yrs21":0.61,"livCou":0.74,"livAus":0.49,"livCen":0.35,"age18":0.45,"age35":0.71},{"text":"Unsure","total":0.09,"yrs05":0.16,"yrs620":0.06,"yrs21":0.08,"livCou":0.09,"livAus":0.1,"livCen":0.07,"age18":0.13,"age35":0.07}]},{"id":"Q6","note":null,"question":"In your opinion, has gentrification helped or hurt your neighborhood?","answers":[{"text":"Helped","total":0.32,"yrs05":0.22,"yrs620":0.46,"yrs21":0.3,"livCou":0.31,"livAus":0.33,"livCen":0.28,"age18":0.36,"age35":0.28},{"text":"Hurt","total":0.44,"yrs05":0.44,"yrs620":0.35,"yrs21":0.48,"livCou":0.37,"livAus":0.47,"livCen":0.45,"age18":0.37,"age35":0.5},{"text":"Unsure","total":0.24,"yrs05":0.34,"yrs620":0.2,"yrs21":0.22,"livCou":0.32,"livAus":0.21,"livCen":0.26,"age18":0.27,"age35":0.22}]},{"id":"Q7","note":null,"question":"Should the City of Austin relax its development rules to allow for more types of housing to be built in the city such as town homes, garage apartments and other small apartment buildings?","answers":[{"text":"Yes","total":0.57,"yrs05":0.63,"yrs620":0.59,"yrs21":0.54,"livCou":0.56,"livAus":0.59,"livCen":0.6,"age18":0.65,"age35":0.53},{"text":"No","total":0.23,"yrs05":0.17,"yrs620":0.23,"yrs21":0.27,"livCou":0.23,"livAus":0.23,"livCen":0.2,"age18":0.16,"age35":0.27},{"text":"Unsure","total":0.19,"yrs05":0.2,"yrs620":0.18,"yrs21":0.2,"livCou":0.21,"livAus":0.18,"livCen":0.21,"age18":0.19,"age35":0.19}]},{"id":"Q8","note":null,"question":"Would you support a 20% homestead exemption?","answers":[{"text":"Yes","total":0.79,"yrs05":0.69,"yrs620":0.82,"yrs21":0.82,"livCou":0.79,"livAus":0.8,"livCen":0.77,"age18":0.75,"age35":0.81},{"text":"No","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.06,"yrs620":0.07,"yrs21":0.08,"livCou":0.07,"livAus":0.07,"livCen":0.07,"age18":0.06,"age35":0.07},{"text":"Unsure","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.25,"yrs620":0.12,"yrs21":0.1,"livCou":0.14,"livAus":0.14,"livCen":0.16,"age18":0.19,"age35":0.11}]},{"id":"Q9","note":null,"question":"Would you support a homestead exemption if it meant raising property taxes for industrial and commercial properties?","answers":[{"text":"Yes","total":0.69,"yrs05":0.57,"yrs620":0.69,"yrs21":0.74,"livCou":0.69,"livAus":0.69,"livCen":0.7,"age18":0.58,"age35":0.74},{"text":"No","total":0.13,"yrs05":0.15,"yrs620":0.13,"yrs21":0.12,"livCou":0.12,"livAus":0.13,"livCen":0.14,"age18":0.14,"age35":0.12},{"text":"Unsure","total":0.18,"yrs05":0.28,"yrs620":0.19,"yrs21":0.14,"livCou":0.19,"livAus":0.18,"livCen":0.16,"age18":0.27,"age35":0.14}]},{"id":"Q10","note":"Reporting Extremely/Very Important","question":"How important do you think the following industries are to Austin's economy?","answers":[{"text":"Technology","total":0.9,"yrs05":0.88,"yrs620":0.94,"yrs21":0.88,"livCou":0.9,"livAus":0.9,"livCen":0.91,"age18":0.9,"age35":0.9},{"text":"Education","total":0.86,"yrs05":0.88,"yrs620":0.82,"yrs21":0.87,"livCou":0.86,"livAus":0.85,"livCen":0.88,"age18":0.84,"age35":0.86},{"text":"Service industry (hotels, retail, restaurants, bars)","total":0.82,"yrs05":0.87,"yrs620":0.83,"yrs21":0.8,"livCou":0.83,"livAus":0.82,"livCen":0.86,"age18":0.85,"age35":0.81},{"text":"Healthcare","total":0.79,"yrs05":0.79,"yrs620":0.76,"yrs21":0.82,"livCou":0.82,"livAus":0.77,"livCen":0.75,"age18":0.79,"age35":0.8},{"text":"Entertainment/Festivals","total":0.78,"yrs05":0.83,"yrs620":0.81,"yrs21":0.75,"livCou":0.79,"livAus":0.78,"livCen":0.82,"age18":0.82,"age35":0.77},{"text":"Entrepreneurial/Business Owner","total":0.77,"yrs05":0.84,"yrs620":0.8,"yrs21":0.73,"livCou":0.77,"livAus":0.78,"livCen":0.84,"age18":0.76,"age35":0.78},{"text":"Transportation","total":0.76,"yrs05":0.81,"yrs620":0.71,"yrs21":0.77,"livCou":0.79,"livAus":0.72,"livCen":0.74,"age18":0.8,"age35":0.74},{"text":"Federal, state or local government","total":0.74,"yrs05":0.73,"yrs620":0.75,"yrs21":0.74,"livCou":0.73,"livAus":0.75,"livCen":0.78,"age18":0.72,"age35":0.75},{"text":"Real estate","total":0.74,"yrs05":0.78,"yrs620":0.68,"yrs21":0.76,"livCou":0.74,"livAus":0.74,"livCen":0.73,"age18":0.77,"age35":0.72},{"text":"Communications","total":0.71,"yrs05":0.74,"yrs620":0.65,"yrs21":0.73,"livCou":0.75,"livAus":0.66,"livCen":0.67,"age18":0.72,"age35":0.7},{"text":"Creative (design, fashion, art, music, writing)","total":0.71,"yrs05":0.77,"yrs620":0.72,"yrs21":0.67,"livCou":0.67,"livAus":0.74,"livCen":0.77,"age18":0.81,"age35":0.65},{"text":"Energy or Utilities","total":0.68,"yrs05":0.71,"yrs620":0.59,"yrs21":0.71,"livCou":0.69,"livAus":0.66,"livCen":0.63,"age18":0.75,"age35":0.64},{"text":"Law/Legal Services","total":0.54,"yrs05":0.6,"yrs620":0.46,"yrs21":0.57,"livCou":0.55,"livAus":0.53,"livCen":0.5,"age18":0.61,"age35":0.51},{"text":"Accounting and Finance","total":0.53,"yrs05":0.57,"yrs620":0.5,"yrs21":0.53,"livCou":0.56,"livAus":0.49,"livCen":0.51,"age18":0.61,"age35":0.49},{"text":"Manufacturing","total":0.51,"yrs05":0.48,"yrs620":0.48,"yrs21":0.55,"livCou":0.57,"livAus":0.45,"livCen":0.38,"age18":0.53,"age35":0.5},{"text":"Oil and Gas","total":0.48,"yrs05":0.53,"yrs620":0.43,"yrs21":0.49,"livCou":0.51,"livAus":0.45,"livCen":0.36,"age18":0.59,"age35":0.42},{"text":"Farming or Agriculture","total":0.38,"yrs05":0.48,"yrs620":0.34,"yrs21":0.37,"livCou":0.42,"livAus":0.35,"livCen":0.34,"age18":0.46,"age35":0.35}]},{"id":"Q11","note":null,"question":"How difficult do you think it is to get a good job in Austin?","answers":[{"text":"Very difficult","total":0.18,"yrs05":0.17,"yrs620":0.14,"yrs21":0.21,"livCou":0.16,"livAus":0.2,"livCen":0.18,"age18":0.16,"age35":0.19},{"text":"Somewhat difficult","total":0.49,"yrs05":0.47,"yrs620":0.47,"yrs21":0.51,"livCou":0.49,"livAus":0.49,"livCen":0.52,"age18":0.53,"age35":0.46},{"text":"Not very difficult","total":0.24,"yrs05":0.26,"yrs620":0.28,"yrs21":0.21,"livCou":0.24,"livAus":0.24,"livCen":0.24,"age18":0.24,"age35":0.24},{"text":"Not difficult at all","total":0.05,"yrs05":0.07,"yrs620":0.07,"yrs21":0.03,"livCou":0.06,"livAus":0.04,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.04,"age35":0.05},{"text":"Don't know","total":0.04,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.05,"yrs21":0.05,"livCou":0.06,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.03,"age35":0.05}]},{"id":"Q12","note":null,"question":"How important do you think start-up companies are to Austin's economy?","answers":[{"text":"Extremely important","total":0.28,"yrs05":0.33,"yrs620":0.31,"yrs21":0.24,"livCou":0.29,"livAus":0.26,"livCen":0.27,"age18":0.34,"age35":0.24},{"text":"Very important","total":0.39,"yrs05":0.37,"yrs620":0.39,"yrs21":0.4,"livCou":0.38,"livAus":0.4,"livCen":0.4,"age18":0.32,"age35":0.42},{"text":"Somewhat important","total":0.28,"yrs05":0.24,"yrs620":0.24,"yrs21":0.32,"livCou":0.25,"livAus":0.31,"livCen":0.28,"age18":0.27,"age35":0.28},{"text":"Not very important","total":0.02,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Not important at all","total":0,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0,"livCen":0,"age18":0.01,"age35":0},{"text":"Don't know","total":0.03,"yrs05":0.05,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0.05,"age35":0.02}]},{"id":"Q13","note":null,"question":"Do you think Austin should create city-specific incentive programs such as grants, tax reductions, loans and fee waivers to attract companies that bring or grow middle class jobs and/or train current residents for middle class jobs?","answers":[{"text":"Yes","total":0.71,"yrs05":0.8,"yrs620":0.71,"yrs21":0.67,"livCou":0.7,"livAus":0.71,"livCen":0.73,"age18":0.79,"age35":0.67},{"text":"No","total":0.15,"yrs05":0.09,"yrs620":0.16,"yrs21":0.18,"livCou":0.16,"livAus":0.14,"livCen":0.13,"age18":0.08,"age35":0.19},{"text":"Unsure","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.11,"yrs620":0.13,"yrs21":0.15,"livCou":0.13,"livAus":0.14,"livCen":0.14,"age18":0.13,"age35":0.14}]},{"id":"Q14","note":null,"question":"Do you support economic incentives for companies that provide manufacturing jobs that pay $60,000 or more annually to existing residents?","answers":[{"text":"Yes, definitely","total":0.35,"yrs05":0.41,"yrs620":0.36,"yrs21":0.32,"livCou":0.39,"livAus":0.31,"livCen":0.34,"age18":0.36,"age35":0.35},{"text":"Yes, somewhat","total":0.36,"yrs05":0.35,"yrs620":0.35,"yrs21":0.37,"livCou":0.34,"livAus":0.38,"livCen":0.36,"age18":0.37,"age35":0.35},{"text":"Not really","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.1,"yrs620":0.16,"yrs21":0.15,"livCou":0.13,"livAus":0.15,"livCen":0.12,"age18":0.09,"age35":0.17},{"text":"Definitely not","total":0.04,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0.04,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.03,"livAus":0.04,"livCen":0.04,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.05},{"text":"Unsure","total":0.11,"yrs05":0.12,"yrs620":0.1,"yrs21":0.12,"livCou":0.1,"livAus":0.12,"livCen":0.14,"age18":0.17,"age35":0.08}]},{"id":"Q15","note":null,"question":"Do you think Austin should provide additional support, like affordable housing and tax incentives, for people in creative industries, such as musicians, entertainers and artists?","answers":[{"text":"Yes, definitely","total":0.26,"yrs05":0.27,"yrs620":0.26,"yrs21":0.25,"livCou":0.24,"livAus":0.28,"livCen":0.36,"age18":0.31,"age35":0.23},{"text":"Yes, somewhat","total":0.28,"yrs05":0.28,"yrs620":0.24,"yrs21":0.3,"livCou":0.27,"livAus":0.29,"livCen":0.28,"age18":0.31,"age35":0.26},{"text":"Not really","total":0.29,"yrs05":0.29,"yrs620":0.29,"yrs21":0.29,"livCou":0.29,"livAus":0.28,"livCen":0.27,"age18":0.25,"age35":0.31},{"text":"Definitely not","total":0.11,"yrs05":0.09,"yrs620":0.13,"yrs21":0.11,"livCou":0.12,"livAus":0.1,"livCen":0.06,"age18":0.06,"age35":0.14},{"text":"Unsure","total":0.06,"yrs05":0.07,"yrs620":0.08,"yrs21":0.05,"livCou":0.08,"livAus":0.05,"livCen":0.04,"age18":0.07,"age35":0.06}]},{"id":"Q16","note":null,"question":"The city of Austin gives companies looking to build in Austin economic incentives if they agree to pay an hourly wage of at least $11 per hour. Do you believe this is the right hourly wage?","answers":[{"text":"Yes, definitely","total":0.42,"yrs05":0.5,"yrs620":0.39,"yrs21":0.41,"livCou":0.41,"livAus":0.44,"livCen":0.49,"age18":0.56,"age35":0.35},{"text":"No, the wage should be more","total":0.37,"yrs05":0.34,"yrs620":0.37,"yrs21":0.38,"livCou":0.34,"livAus":0.4,"livCen":0.4,"age18":0.27,"age35":0.42},{"text":"No, the wage should be less","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.04,"yrs620":0.08,"yrs21":0.07,"livCou":0.09,"livAus":0.04,"livCen":0.02,"age18":0.06,"age35":0.07},{"text":"Unsure","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.12,"yrs620":0.16,"yrs21":0.14,"livCou":0.17,"livAus":0.12,"livCen":0.09,"age18":0.11,"age35":0.16}]},{"id":"Q17","note":null,"question":"How optimistic or pessimistic are you about the newly elected representatives in the mayor's office?","answers":[{"text":"Very optimistic","total":0.06,"yrs05":0.06,"yrs620":0.06,"yrs21":0.05,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0.06,"livCen":0.05,"age18":0.07,"age35":0.05},{"text":"Somewhat optimistic","total":0.32,"yrs05":0.25,"yrs620":0.34,"yrs21":0.35,"livCou":0.33,"livAus":0.32,"livCen":0.35,"age18":0.25,"age35":0.36},{"text":"Somewhat pessimistic","total":0.19,"yrs05":0.14,"yrs620":0.19,"yrs21":0.2,"livCou":0.16,"livAus":0.22,"livCen":0.19,"age18":0.16,"age35":0.2},{"text":"Very pessimistic","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.05,"yrs620":0.08,"yrs21":0.06,"livCou":0.06,"livAus":0.07,"livCen":0.08,"age18":0.07,"age35":0.06},{"text":"Unfamiliar","total":0.23,"yrs05":0.34,"yrs620":0.2,"yrs21":0.19,"livCou":0.25,"livAus":0.21,"livCen":0.2,"age18":0.32,"age35":0.18},{"text":"Undecided","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.16,"yrs620":0.12,"yrs21":0.15,"livCou":0.15,"livAus":0.13,"livCen":0.12,"age18":0.14,"age35":0.14}]},{"id":"Q18","note":null,"question":"How optimistic or pessimistic are you about the newly elected representatives in City Council?","answers":[{"text":"Very optimistic","total":0.04,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.04,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.02,"age18":0.04,"age35":0.03},{"text":"Somewhat optimistic","total":0.31,"yrs05":0.24,"yrs620":0.34,"yrs21":0.32,"livCou":0.29,"livAus":0.33,"livCen":0.38,"age18":0.25,"age35":0.34},{"text":"Somewhat pessimistic","total":0.19,"yrs05":0.15,"yrs620":0.2,"yrs21":0.21,"livCou":0.18,"livAus":0.2,"livCen":0.19,"age18":0.17,"age35":0.21},{"text":"Very pessimistic","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.04,"yrs620":0.1,"yrs21":0.07,"livCou":0.06,"livAus":0.08,"livCen":0.08,"age18":0.05,"age35":0.08},{"text":"Unfamiliar","total":0.26,"yrs05":0.41,"yrs620":0.22,"yrs21":0.22,"livCou":0.29,"livAus":0.23,"livCen":0.22,"age18":0.37,"age35":0.2},{"text":"Undecided","total":0.13,"yrs05":0.13,"yrs620":0.12,"yrs21":0.13,"livCou":0.14,"livAus":0.12,"livCen":0.11,"age18":0.12,"age35":0.14}]},{"id":"Q19","note":null,"question":"The city of Austin is now divided into 10 single member districts, each with its own council member, and one mayor who is voted on at-large.  How optimistic or pessimistic are you about the new 10-1 City Council structure?","answers":[{"text":"Very optimistic","total":0.09,"yrs05":0.08,"yrs620":0.09,"yrs21":0.1,"livCou":0.09,"livAus":0.09,"livCen":0.09,"age18":0.1,"age35":0.09},{"text":"Somewhat optimistic","total":0.34,"yrs05":0.28,"yrs620":0.4,"yrs21":0.33,"livCou":0.31,"livAus":0.37,"livCen":0.42,"age18":0.24,"age35":0.4},{"text":"Somewhat pessimistic","total":0.15,"yrs05":0.15,"yrs620":0.11,"yrs21":0.18,"livCou":0.15,"livAus":0.16,"livCen":0.13,"age18":0.16,"age35":0.15},{"text":"Very pessimistic","total":0.06,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.07,"yrs21":0.06,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0.06,"livCen":0.06,"age18":0.05,"age35":0.06},{"text":"Unfamiliar","total":0.22,"yrs05":0.37,"yrs620":0.2,"yrs21":0.16,"livCou":0.24,"livAus":0.19,"livCen":0.17,"age18":0.31,"age35":0.17},{"text":"Undecided","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.1,"yrs620":0.12,"yrs21":0.17,"livCou":0.15,"livAus":0.13,"livCen":0.12,"age18":0.14,"age35":0.14}]},{"id":"Q20","note":null,"question":"How supportive are you of the coming Innovation Zone in the northeast corner of downtown? This zone will include Austin's new medical school and teaching hospital among other additions.","answers":[{"text":"Very supportive","total":0.23,"yrs05":0.23,"yrs620":0.25,"yrs21":0.21,"livCou":0.24,"livAus":0.23,"livCen":0.24,"age18":0.28,"age35":0.2},{"text":"Somewhat supportive","total":0.28,"yrs05":0.25,"yrs620":0.29,"yrs21":0.28,"livCou":0.27,"livAus":0.29,"livCen":0.25,"age18":0.24,"age35":0.3},{"text":"Neutral","total":0.23,"yrs05":0.2,"yrs620":0.2,"yrs21":0.26,"livCou":0.23,"livAus":0.24,"livCen":0.25,"age18":0.19,"age35":0.26},{"text":"Somewhat unsupportive","total":0.04,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0.05,"yrs21":0.05,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.06,"livCen":0.05,"age18":0.04,"age35":0.04},{"text":"Very unsupportive","total":0.03,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0.04,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.04},{"text":"Unfamiliar","total":0.15,"yrs05":0.24,"yrs620":0.12,"yrs21":0.13,"livCou":0.17,"livAus":0.13,"livCen":0.14,"age18":0.21,"age35":0.12},{"text":"Undecided","total":0.04,"yrs05":0.04,"yrs620":0.04,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.04,"age35":0.04}]},{"id":"Q21","note":null,"question":"How familiar are you with the \"10 Goals in 10 Years\" effort (also known as \"10-10\")? This effort officially kicked off several years ago, and is related to enhancing Austin's economic, healthcare, and technology infrastructure over the coming decade.","answers":[{"text":"Very familiar","total":0.05,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.06,"yrs21":0.05,"livCou":0.04,"livAus":0.06,"livCen":0.09,"age18":0.07,"age35":0.04},{"text":"Somewhat familiar","total":0.23,"yrs05":0.23,"yrs620":0.24,"yrs21":0.21,"livCou":0.22,"livAus":0.23,"livCen":0.17,"age18":0.26,"age35":0.21},{"text":"Unfamiliar","total":0.72,"yrs05":0.74,"yrs620":0.7,"yrs21":0.74,"livCou":0.74,"livAus":0.71,"livCen":0.74,"age18":0.67,"age35":0.75}]},{"id":"Q22","note":"Reporting Very/Somewhat Supportive","question":"Assuming an increase in taxes for projects that involve lots of new construction, how supportive are you of the following transportation initiatives/infrastructure projects?","answers":[{"text":"More dedicated express lanes on Austin's major highways","total":0.7,"yrs05":0.71,"yrs620":0.69,"yrs21":0.71,"livCou":0.74,"livAus":0.66,"livCen":0.64,"age18":0.71,"age35":0.7},{"text":"Expanding service on the most frequently used bus routes","total":0.69,"yrs05":0.77,"yrs620":0.69,"yrs21":0.66,"livCou":0.64,"livAus":0.75,"livCen":0.77,"age18":0.69,"age35":0.69},{"text":"Above ground rail system","total":0.63,"yrs05":0.71,"yrs620":0.65,"yrs21":0.59,"livCou":0.61,"livAus":0.66,"livCen":0.66,"age18":0.65,"age35":0.62},{"text":"Underground subway system","total":0.52,"yrs05":0.62,"yrs620":0.52,"yrs21":0.47,"livCou":0.48,"livAus":0.56,"livCen":0.58,"age18":0.61,"age35":0.47},{"text":"Dedicated bicycle lanes throughout major Austin roadways","total":0.49,"yrs05":0.57,"yrs620":0.51,"yrs21":0.44,"livCou":0.44,"livAus":0.54,"livCen":0.6,"age18":0.54,"age35":0.46},{"text":"Moving I-35 underground","total":0.47,"yrs05":0.47,"yrs620":0.49,"yrs21":0.45,"livCou":0.44,"livAus":0.5,"livCen":0.51,"age18":0.53,"age35":0.44},{"text":"Converting lanes in the downtown area to be for buses only","total":0.41,"yrs05":0.37,"yrs620":0.45,"yrs21":0.42,"livCou":0.4,"livAus":0.43,"livCen":0.45,"age18":0.47,"age35":0.39}]},{"id":"Q23","note":null,"question":"Do you think the Austin Police Department treats people of all races and ethnicities fairly and equally?","answers":[{"text":"Yes, definitely","total":0.22,"yrs05":0.27,"yrs620":0.2,"yrs21":0.2,"livCou":0.25,"livAus":0.18,"livCen":0.13,"age18":0.22,"age35":0.21},{"text":"Yes, somewhat","total":0.32,"yrs05":0.22,"yrs620":0.31,"yrs21":0.37,"livCou":0.33,"livAus":0.31,"livCen":0.32,"age18":0.31,"age35":0.32},{"text":"Not really","total":0.2,"yrs05":0.18,"yrs620":0.24,"yrs21":0.2,"livCou":0.18,"livAus":0.23,"livCen":0.22,"age18":0.2,"age35":0.21},{"text":"Definitely not","total":0.12,"yrs05":0.08,"yrs620":0.13,"yrs21":0.13,"livCou":0.09,"livAus":0.16,"livCen":0.19,"age18":0.1,"age35":0.13},{"text":"Unsure","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.26,"yrs620":0.12,"yrs21":0.1,"livCou":0.16,"livAus":0.13,"livCen":0.14,"age18":0.18,"age35":0.12}]},{"id":"Q24","note":null,"question":"Do you think APD officers should be equipped with body cameras?","answers":[{"text":"Yes","total":0.82,"yrs05":0.79,"yrs620":0.82,"yrs21":0.84,"livCou":0.85,"livAus":0.79,"livCen":0.79,"age18":0.76,"age35":0.85},{"text":"No","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.12,"yrs620":0.05,"yrs21":0.05,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0.09,"livCen":0.09,"age18":0.08,"age35":0.06},{"text":"Unsure","total":0.11,"yrs05":0.09,"yrs620":0.13,"yrs21":0.11,"livCou":0.1,"livAus":0.12,"livCen":0.12,"age18":0.16,"age35":0.09}]},{"id":"Q25","note":null,"question":"Which of the following do you support?","answers":[{"text":"State policies to legalize same-sex marriage","total":0.55,"yrs05":0.62,"yrs620":0.53,"yrs21":0.53,"livCou":0.45,"livAus":0.65,"livCen":0.8,"age18":0.62,"age35":0.51},{"text":"State policies to legalize marijuana","total":0.52,"yrs05":0.51,"yrs620":0.47,"yrs21":0.56,"livCou":0.44,"livAus":0.6,"livCen":0.67,"age18":0.57,"age35":0.5},{"text":"State policies to lessen the impact of climate change","total":0.49,"yrs05":0.58,"yrs620":0.47,"yrs21":0.47,"livCou":0.41,"livAus":0.58,"livCen":0.65,"age18":0.57,"age35":0.45},{"text":"Allowing religious artifacts (e.g., Ten Commandments display) in public spaces","total":0.45,"yrs05":0.39,"yrs620":0.45,"yrs21":0.48,"livCou":0.52,"livAus":0.37,"livCen":0.29,"age18":0.36,"age35":0.5},{"text":"Allowing religious activities (e.g., prayer) in government supported institutions (e.g., schools)","total":0.44,"yrs05":0.44,"yrs620":0.43,"yrs21":0.46,"livCou":0.54,"livAus":0.35,"livCen":0.31,"age18":0.37,"age35":0.48},{"text":"Policies to change or end the Affordable Care Act (ObamaCare)","total":0.41,"yrs05":0.37,"yrs620":0.38,"yrs21":0.45,"livCou":0.49,"livAus":0.33,"livCen":0.22,"age18":0.43,"age35":0.4},{"text":"None of the above","total":0.05,"yrs05":0.04,"yrs620":0.06,"yrs21":0.05,"livCou":0.07,"livAus":0.04,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.05,"age35":0.05}]},{"id":"Q26","note":null,"question":"In which of the following school districts do your children currently attend school?","answers":[{"text":"Austin (AISD)","total":0.32,"yrs05":0.16,"yrs620":0.29,"yrs21":0.39,"livCou":0.07,"livAus":0.65,"livCen":0.83,"age18":0.32,"age35":0.33},{"text":"Round Rock","total":0.12,"yrs05":0.08,"yrs620":0.11,"yrs21":0.14,"livCou":0.18,"livAus":0.05,"livCen":0,"age18":0.11,"age35":0.13},{"text":"Leander","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.16,"yrs620":0.11,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.12,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0,"age18":0.06,"age35":0.08},{"text":"Pflugerville","total":0.05,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0.05,"yrs21":0.07,"livCou":0.07,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0,"age18":0.04,"age35":0.05},{"text":"Luling","total":0.03,"yrs05":0.1,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.06,"livAus":0,"livCen":0,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.04},{"text":"Manor","total":0.03,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0.08,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.04},{"text":"Del Valle","total":0.03,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0.06,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0.05,"livCen":0.05,"age18":0,"age35":0.05},{"text":"Hays","total":0.03,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0.05,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0,"livCen":0,"age18":0.05,"age35":0.01},{"text":"Georgetown","total":0.03,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0.02,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0,"livCen":0,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.03},{"text":"San Marcos","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.04,"yrs620":0.02,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0.03,"livAus":0,"livCen":0,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Lockhart","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.07,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0,"livCou":0.03,"livAus":0,"livCen":0,"age18":0,"age35":0.03},{"text":"Bastrop","total":0.02,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0.03,"livCou":0.03,"livAus":0,"livCen":0,"age18":0,"age35":0.03},{"text":"Taylor","total":0.02,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.03,"livAus":0,"livCen":0,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.01},{"text":"Lake Travis","total":0.01,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Eanes","total":0.01,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0,"livCou":0,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.07,"age18":0,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Lago Vista","total":0.01,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0,"livCen":0,"age18":0,"age35":0.01},{"text":"Johnson","total":0,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0,"livCou":0,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0,"age18":0.01,"age35":0},{"text":"Dripping Springs","total":0,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0,"livCou":0,"livAus":0,"livCen":0,"age18":0,"age35":0},{"text":"Other","total":0.03,"yrs05":0.04,"yrs620":0.04,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.04,"livCen":0.02,"age18":0.04,"age35":0.02},{"text":"None of the above","total":0.16,"yrs05":0.33,"yrs620":0.18,"yrs21":0.09,"livCou":0.18,"livAus":0.13,"livCen":0.02,"age18":0.28,"age35":0.08}]},{"id":"Q27","note":null,"question":"Given the amount you pay in taxes, do you believe your children are getting a public education commensurate with your personal financial investment?","answers":[{"text":"Yes, definitely","total":0.21,"yrs05":0.25,"yrs620":0.17,"yrs21":0.23,"livCou":0.26,"livAus":0.16,"livCen":0.19,"age18":0.18,"age35":0.24},{"text":"Yes, somewhat","total":0.33,"yrs05":0.22,"yrs620":0.33,"yrs21":0.37,"livCou":0.36,"livAus":0.3,"livCen":0.38,"age18":0.33,"age35":0.34},{"text":"Not really","total":0.21,"yrs05":0.2,"yrs620":0.19,"yrs21":0.22,"livCou":0.2,"livAus":0.21,"livCen":0.18,"age18":0.11,"age35":0.27},{"text":"Definitely not","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.09,"yrs620":0.11,"yrs21":0.17,"livCou":0.08,"livAus":0.21,"livCen":0.23,"age18":0.2,"age35":0.1},{"text":"Unsure","total":0.11,"yrs05":0.24,"yrs620":0.18,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.1,"livAus":0.12,"livCen":0.02,"age18":0.18,"age35":0.05}]},{"id":"Q28","note":null,"question":"Why do you believe your child/children are not getting a public education commensurate with your financial investment?","answers":[{"text":"Educational opportunities aren't adequate","total":0.68,"yrs05":0.85,"yrs620":0.69,"yrs21":0.64,"livCou":0.63,"livAus":0.72,"livCen":0.75,"age18":0.76,"age35":0.64},{"text":"The facilities are run down/need improvement","total":0.38,"yrs05":0.49,"yrs620":0.3,"yrs21":0.4,"livCou":0.23,"livAus":0.52,"livCen":0.54,"age18":0.42,"age35":0.36},{"text":"Costs too much","total":0.25,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0.46,"yrs21":0.21,"livCou":0.29,"livAus":0.22,"livCen":0.12,"age18":0.16,"age35":0.3},{"text":"The schools my child/children attend aren't safe","total":0.22,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.36,"livCou":0.1,"livAus":0.32,"livCen":0.27,"age18":0.23,"age35":0.21},{"text":"Other","total":0.11,"yrs05":0.07,"yrs620":0.09,"yrs21":0.13,"livCou":0.15,"livAus":0.08,"livCen":0.13,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.16}]},{"id":"Q29","note":null,"question":"If financially feasible, would you send your child/children to private school (a school established by a private group rather than by a government entity, usually charging tuition and often guided by a particular philosophy or viewpoint) instead of public school?","answers":[{"text":"Yes, my child/children currently attend private school","total":0.11,"yrs05":0.04,"yrs620":0.04,"yrs21":0.17,"livCou":0.13,"livAus":0.07,"livCen":0.06,"age18":0.12,"age35":0.1},{"text":"Yes, I would send them to private school","total":0.49,"yrs05":0.61,"yrs620":0.4,"yrs21":0.52,"livCou":0.45,"livAus":0.55,"livCen":0.5,"age18":0.64,"age35":0.39},{"text":"No","total":0.26,"yrs05":0.14,"yrs620":0.36,"yrs21":0.24,"livCou":0.26,"livAus":0.27,"livCen":0.32,"age18":0.14,"age35":0.35},{"text":"Unsure","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.21,"yrs620":0.2,"yrs21":0.07,"livCou":0.16,"livAus":0.1,"livCen":0.12,"age18":0.1,"age35":0.16}]},{"id":"Q30","note":null,"question":"A charter school is a school that receives public funding but operates independently of the established public school system in its area. Would you send your child/children to a charter school?","answers":[{"text":"Yes, my child/children currently attend a charter school","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.06,"yrs620":0.04,"yrs21":0.08,"livCou":0.06,"livAus":0.08,"livCen":0.07,"age18":0.08,"age35":0.05},{"text":"Yes, I would consider/am considering sending them to a charter school","total":0.53,"yrs05":0.55,"yrs620":0.43,"yrs21":0.59,"livCou":0.51,"livAus":0.56,"livCen":0.48,"age18":0.51,"age35":0.54},{"text":"No","total":0.28,"yrs05":0.15,"yrs620":0.39,"yrs21":0.25,"livCou":0.28,"livAus":0.27,"livCen":0.4,"age18":0.24,"age35":0.3},{"text":"Unsure","total":0.13,"yrs05":0.24,"yrs620":0.14,"yrs21":0.08,"livCou":0.16,"livAus":0.09,"livCen":0.06,"age18":0.16,"age35":0.1}]},{"id":"Q31","note":null,"question":"Did the schools in your neighborhood influence where you and your family chose to buy or rent a place to live?","answers":[{"text":"Yes, definitely","total":0.4,"yrs05":0.33,"yrs620":0.45,"yrs21":0.4,"livCou":0.41,"livAus":0.39,"livCen":0.45,"age18":0.39,"age35":0.41},{"text":"Yes, somewhat","total":0.2,"yrs05":0.36,"yrs620":0.19,"yrs21":0.15,"livCou":0.24,"livAus":0.15,"livCen":0.14,"age18":0.17,"age35":0.22},{"text":"Not really","total":0.27,"yrs05":0.12,"yrs620":0.27,"yrs21":0.31,"livCou":0.27,"livAus":0.27,"livCen":0.2,"age18":0.32,"age35":0.24},{"text":"Definitely not","total":0.09,"yrs05":0.14,"yrs620":0.05,"yrs21":0.09,"livCou":0.04,"livAus":0.15,"livCen":0.15,"age18":0.06,"age35":0.11},{"text":"Unsure","total":0.04,"yrs05":0.04,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.04,"livAus":0.04,"livCen":0.06,"age18":0.06,"age35":0.03}]},{"id":"Q32","note":null,"question":"Do you support state vouchers that would allow public school students to channel public funding to the private school of their choice?","answers":[{"text":"Yes, definitely","total":0.32,"yrs05":0.15,"yrs620":0.26,"yrs21":0.42,"livCou":0.35,"livAus":0.29,"livCen":0.31,"age18":0.43,"age35":0.25},{"text":"Yes, somewhat","total":0.22,"yrs05":0.17,"yrs620":0.28,"yrs21":0.19,"livCou":0.23,"livAus":0.2,"livCen":0.17,"age18":0.16,"age35":0.25},{"text":"Not really","total":0.16,"yrs05":0.12,"yrs620":0.16,"yrs21":0.16,"livCou":0.15,"livAus":0.17,"livCen":0.21,"age18":0.15,"age35":0.16},{"text":"Definitely not","total":0.13,"yrs05":0.07,"yrs620":0.17,"yrs21":0.12,"livCou":0.08,"livAus":0.19,"livCen":0.21,"age18":0.04,"age35":0.18},{"text":"Unsure","total":0.18,"yrs05":0.5,"yrs620":0.13,"yrs21":0.11,"livCou":0.2,"livAus":0.15,"livCen":0.1,"age18":0.22,"age35":0.15}]},{"id":"Q33","note":"Reporting Strongly/Somewhat Agree","question":"How much do you agree or disagree that the following characteristics describe the City of Austin?","answers":[{"text":"Musical","total":0.94,"yrs05":0.94,"yrs620":0.97,"yrs21":0.92,"livCou":0.94,"livAus":0.94,"livCen":0.95,"age18":0.93,"age35":0.95},{"text":"Active","total":0.9,"yrs05":0.93,"yrs620":0.92,"yrs21":0.87,"livCou":0.87,"livAus":0.93,"livCen":0.97,"age18":0.9,"age35":0.9},{"text":"Artistic","total":0.89,"yrs05":0.9,"yrs620":0.9,"yrs21":0.88,"livCou":0.87,"livAus":0.91,"livCen":0.95,"age18":0.89,"age35":0.89},{"text":"Creative","total":0.89,"yrs05":0.88,"yrs620":0.91,"yrs21":0.88,"livCou":0.86,"livAus":0.91,"livCen":0.93,"age18":0.88,"age35":0.89},{"text":"Technologically sophisticated","total":0.87,"yrs05":0.84,"yrs620":0.88,"yrs21":0.88,"livCou":0.84,"livAus":0.9,"livCen":0.91,"age18":0.84,"age35":0.88},{"text":"Innovative","total":0.82,"yrs05":0.82,"yrs620":0.85,"yrs21":0.81,"livCou":0.77,"livAus":0.87,"livCen":0.89,"age18":0.82,"age35":0.82},{"text":"Entrepreneurial","total":0.81,"yrs05":0.83,"yrs620":0.81,"yrs21":0.79,"livCou":0.77,"livAus":0.84,"livCen":0.88,"age18":0.78,"age35":0.82},{"text":"Environmentally friendly","total":0.79,"yrs05":0.77,"yrs620":0.81,"yrs21":0.79,"livCou":0.74,"livAus":0.85,"livCen":0.85,"age18":0.79,"age35":0.8},{"text":"Young","total":0.77,"yrs05":0.8,"yrs620":0.79,"yrs21":0.75,"livCou":0.75,"livAus":0.8,"livCen":0.87,"age18":0.84,"age35":0.74},{"text":"Liberal","total":0.75,"yrs05":0.8,"yrs620":0.74,"yrs21":0.74,"livCou":0.73,"livAus":0.78,"livCen":0.81,"age18":0.75,"age35":0.76},{"text":"Culturally diverse","total":0.74,"yrs05":0.79,"yrs620":0.68,"yrs21":0.76,"livCou":0.76,"livAus":0.72,"livCen":0.72,"age18":0.77,"age35":0.73},{"text":"Laid back","total":0.72,"yrs05":0.74,"yrs620":0.73,"yrs21":0.7,"livCou":0.69,"livAus":0.74,"livCen":0.77,"age18":0.79,"age35":0.68},{"text":"Hipsterish","total":0.71,"yrs05":0.8,"yrs620":0.7,"yrs21":0.68,"livCou":0.65,"livAus":0.77,"livCen":0.84,"age18":0.81,"age35":0.66},{"text":"Weird","total":0.69,"yrs05":0.7,"yrs620":0.66,"yrs21":0.69,"livCou":0.69,"livAus":0.68,"livCen":0.7,"age18":0.74,"age35":0.66},{"text":"Philanthropic","total":0.55,"yrs05":0.54,"yrs620":0.54,"yrs21":0.56,"livCou":0.54,"livAus":0.55,"livCen":0.62,"age18":0.59,"age35":0.53},{"text":"Segregated","total":0.45,"yrs05":0.38,"yrs620":0.5,"yrs21":0.44,"livCou":0.37,"livAus":0.54,"livCen":0.62,"age18":0.42,"age35":0.46},{"text":"Narcissistic","total":0.42,"yrs05":0.44,"yrs620":0.37,"yrs21":0.43,"livCou":0.38,"livAus":0.45,"livCen":0.5,"age18":0.4,"age35":0.43},{"text":"Spiritual","total":0.39,"yrs05":0.4,"yrs620":0.37,"yrs21":0.4,"livCou":0.36,"livAus":0.42,"livCen":0.39,"age18":0.46,"age35":0.35},{"text":"Unequal","total":0.32,"yrs05":0.22,"yrs620":0.31,"yrs21":0.37,"livCou":0.27,"livAus":0.36,"livCen":0.45,"age18":0.29,"age35":0.33},{"text":"Religious","total":0.29,"yrs05":0.23,"yrs620":0.27,"yrs21":0.34,"livCou":0.31,"livAus":0.28,"livCen":0.26,"age18":0.26,"age35":0.31},{"text":"Conservative","total":0.25,"yrs05":0.17,"yrs620":0.25,"yrs21":0.29,"livCou":0.24,"livAus":0.26,"livCen":0.21,"age18":0.25,"age35":0.25},{"text":"Affordable","total":0.24,"yrs05":0.33,"yrs620":0.23,"yrs21":0.21,"livCou":0.26,"livAus":0.22,"livCen":0.25,"age18":0.32,"age35":0.2}]},{"id":"Q34","note":"Reporting Strongly/Somewhat Agree","question":"How much do you agree or disagree that the following characteristics describe yourself?","answers":[{"text":"Laid back","total":0.75,"yrs05":0.77,"yrs620":0.69,"yrs21":0.77,"livCou":0.72,"livAus":0.78,"livCen":0.83,"age18":0.83,"age35":0.71},{"text":"Environmentally friendly","total":0.74,"yrs05":0.71,"yrs620":0.71,"yrs21":0.78,"livCou":0.71,"livAus":0.78,"livCen":0.77,"age18":0.72,"age35":0.75},{"text":"Active","total":0.69,"yrs05":0.7,"yrs620":0.7,"yrs21":0.67,"livCou":0.67,"livAus":0.7,"livCen":0.74,"age18":0.75,"age35":0.65},{"text":"Creative","total":0.65,"yrs05":0.69,"yrs620":0.63,"yrs21":0.64,"livCou":0.62,"livAus":0.67,"livCen":0.71,"age18":0.73,"age35":0.6},{"text":"Technologically sophisticated","total":0.62,"yrs05":0.65,"yrs620":0.59,"yrs21":0.63,"livCou":0.6,"livAus":0.65,"livCen":0.67,"age18":0.7,"age35":0.58},{"text":"Spiritual","total":0.56,"yrs05":0.52,"yrs620":0.53,"yrs21":0.59,"livCou":0.58,"livAus":0.53,"livCen":0.46,"age18":0.5,"age35":0.59},{"text":"Innovative","total":0.52,"yrs05":0.55,"yrs620":0.51,"yrs21":0.52,"livCou":0.48,"livAus":0.56,"livCen":0.64,"age18":0.6,"age35":0.48},{"text":"Liberal","total":0.5,"yrs05":0.52,"yrs620":0.47,"yrs21":0.52,"livCou":0.39,"livAus":0.63,"livCen":0.73,"age18":0.57,"age35":0.47},{"text":"Artistic","total":0.46,"yrs05":0.47,"yrs620":0.42,"yrs21":0.48,"livCou":0.41,"livAus":0.5,"livCen":0.52,"age18":0.57,"age35":0.39},{"text":"Religious","total":0.45,"yrs05":0.41,"yrs620":0.43,"yrs21":0.49,"livCou":0.47,"livAus":0.43,"livCen":0.33,"age18":0.41,"age35":0.48},{"text":"Musical","total":0.45,"yrs05":0.46,"yrs620":0.45,"yrs21":0.45,"livCou":0.41,"livAus":0.5,"livCen":0.51,"age18":0.58,"age35":0.38},{"text":"Conservative","total":0.43,"yrs05":0.42,"yrs620":0.44,"yrs21":0.43,"livCou":0.51,"livAus":0.35,"livCen":0.27,"age18":0.39,"age35":0.45},{"text":"Weird","total":0.4,"yrs05":0.48,"yrs620":0.32,"yrs21":0.41,"livCou":0.35,"livAus":0.45,"livCen":0.53,"age18":0.57,"age35":0.31},{"text":"Young","total":0.4,"yrs05":0.57,"yrs620":0.32,"yrs21":0.37,"livCou":0.31,"livAus":0.49,"livCen":0.57,"age18":0.82,"age35":0.17},{"text":"Entrepreneurial","total":0.37,"yrs05":0.41,"yrs620":0.36,"yrs21":0.37,"livCou":0.35,"livAus":0.4,"livCen":0.43,"age18":0.43,"age35":0.34},{"text":"Philanthropic","total":0.37,"yrs05":0.33,"yrs620":0.36,"yrs21":0.39,"livCou":0.34,"livAus":0.4,"livCen":0.42,"age18":0.38,"age35":0.36},{"text":"Hipsterish","total":0.19,"yrs05":0.24,"yrs620":0.14,"yrs21":0.2,"livCou":0.17,"livAus":0.21,"livCen":0.26,"age18":0.3,"age35":0.13},{"text":"Narcissistic","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.2,"yrs620":0.11,"yrs21":0.13,"livCou":0.12,"livAus":0.15,"livCen":0.19,"age18":0.21,"age35":0.1}]},{"id":"Q35","note":null,"question":"Which three landmarks do you most strongly associate with Austin?","answers":[{"text":"The Texas State Capitol","total":0.51,"yrs05":0.53,"yrs620":0.55,"yrs21":0.49,"livCou":0.5,"livAus":0.53,"livCen":0.5,"age18":0.51,"age35":0.52},{"text":"University of Texas Tower","total":0.37,"yrs05":0.32,"yrs620":0.36,"yrs21":0.39,"livCou":0.33,"livAus":0.41,"livCen":0.4,"age18":0.33,"age35":0.38},{"text":"6th Street","total":0.32,"yrs05":0.44,"yrs620":0.36,"yrs21":0.25,"livCou":0.33,"livAus":0.32,"livCen":0.29,"age18":0.39,"age35":0.29},{"text":"Zilker Park","total":0.23,"yrs05":0.21,"yrs620":0.17,"yrs21":0.27,"livCou":0.2,"livAus":0.26,"livCen":0.28,"age18":0.26,"age35":0.21},{"text":"Lady Bird Lake/Town Lake and Butler Hike","total":0.22,"yrs05":0.24,"yrs620":0.2,"yrs21":0.22,"livCou":0.18,"livAus":0.25,"livCen":0.3,"age18":0.27,"age35":0.19},{"text":"Barton Springs Pool","total":0.19,"yrs05":0.15,"yrs620":0.12,"yrs21":0.25,"livCou":0.17,"livAus":0.2,"livCen":0.25,"age18":0.15,"age35":0.21},{"text":"Ann W. Richards Congress Avenue Bridge (Bat Bridge)","total":0.18,"yrs05":0.21,"yrs620":0.2,"yrs21":0.16,"livCou":0.16,"livAus":0.2,"livCen":0.16,"age18":0.14,"age35":0.2},{"text":"Darrell K Royal Texas Memorial Stadium","total":0.15,"yrs05":0.12,"yrs620":0.11,"yrs21":0.18,"livCou":0.18,"livAus":0.12,"livCen":0.1,"age18":0.16,"age35":0.14},{"text":"Pennybacker/360 Bridge","total":0.13,"yrs05":0.05,"yrs620":0.18,"yrs21":0.14,"livCou":0.15,"livAus":0.12,"livCen":0.09,"age18":0.12,"age35":0.14},{"text":"Lake Travis","total":0.12,"yrs05":0.12,"yrs620":0.14,"yrs21":0.1,"livCou":0.17,"livAus":0.06,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.09,"age35":0.13},{"text":"Frost Bank Tower","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.08,"yrs620":0.1,"yrs21":0.05,"livCou":0.07,"livAus":0.08,"livCen":0.1,"age18":0.1,"age35":0.06},{"text":"Mount Bonnell","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.05,"yrs620":0.05,"yrs21":0.09,"livCou":0.09,"livAus":0.04,"livCen":0.06,"age18":0.07,"age35":0.07},{"text":"Stevie Ray Vaughan Statue","total":0.06,"yrs05":0.04,"yrs620":0.06,"yrs21":0.08,"livCou":0.07,"livAus":0.06,"livCen":0.06,"age18":0.05,"age35":0.07},{"text":"The Bullock Texas State History Museum","total":0.05,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0.04,"yrs21":0.06,"livCou":0.04,"livAus":0.05,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.03,"age35":0.05},{"text":"The Driskill Hotel","total":0.04,"yrs05":0.05,"yrs620":0.04,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.04,"livAus":0.04,"livCen":0.05,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.05},{"text":"The Moody Theater (ACL Live)","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0.04,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.03},{"text":"Graffiti Park at Castle Hills (Baylor Street)","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.04,"age18":0.05,"age35":0.01},{"text":"Texas Governor's Mansion","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0,"age18":0.03,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Long Center","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0.02,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.02,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Rainey Street","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.03,"age35":0.01},{"text":"LBJ Presidential Library","total":0.01,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.01}]},{"id":"Q36","note":"Select up to five","question":"Which of the following brands do you think are most representative for Austin's identity?","answers":[{"text":"The University of Texas at Austin","total":0.61,"yrs05":0.65,"yrs620":0.54,"yrs21":0.63,"livCou":0.6,"livAus":0.62,"livCen":0.59,"age18":0.59,"age35":0.62},{"text":"Austin City Limits Music Festival","total":0.5,"yrs05":0.55,"yrs620":0.49,"yrs21":0.49,"livCou":0.52,"livAus":0.48,"livCen":0.51,"age18":0.47,"age35":0.52},{"text":"SXSW (South by Southwest)","total":0.46,"yrs05":0.53,"yrs620":0.5,"yrs21":0.4,"livCou":0.46,"livAus":0.46,"livCen":0.44,"age18":0.46,"age35":0.46},{"text":"Dell","total":0.32,"yrs05":0.3,"yrs620":0.37,"yrs21":0.29,"livCou":0.37,"livAus":0.26,"livCen":0.23,"age18":0.2,"age35":0.38},{"text":"Whole Foods Market","total":0.31,"yrs05":0.32,"yrs620":0.37,"yrs21":0.28,"livCou":0.31,"livAus":0.32,"livCen":0.38,"age18":0.29,"age35":0.33},{"text":"Alamo Drafthouse Cinema","total":0.29,"yrs05":0.3,"yrs620":0.35,"yrs21":0.26,"livCou":0.29,"livAus":0.3,"livCen":0.28,"age18":0.35,"age35":0.26},{"text":"Capital City of Texas","total":0.29,"yrs05":0.27,"yrs620":0.3,"yrs21":0.29,"livCou":0.29,"livAus":0.29,"livCen":0.29,"age18":0.23,"age35":0.32},{"text":"Amy's Ice Creams","total":0.19,"yrs05":0.16,"yrs620":0.15,"yrs21":0.22,"livCou":0.13,"livAus":0.24,"livCen":0.23,"age18":0.23,"age35":0.16},{"text":"Broken Spoke Dance Hall","total":0.16,"yrs05":0.12,"yrs620":0.11,"yrs21":0.22,"livCou":0.18,"livAus":0.14,"livCen":0.12,"age18":0.08,"age35":0.21},{"text":"Chuy's","total":0.15,"yrs05":0.12,"yrs620":0.17,"yrs21":0.14,"livCou":0.17,"livAus":0.13,"livCen":0.11,"age18":0.16,"age35":0.14},{"text":"Torchy's Tacos","total":0.15,"yrs05":0.24,"yrs620":0.15,"yrs21":0.11,"livCou":0.08,"livAus":0.22,"livCen":0.24,"age18":0.25,"age35":0.09},{"text":"Kerbey Lane Cafe","total":0.11,"yrs05":0.17,"yrs620":0.11,"yrs21":0.09,"livCou":0.1,"livAus":0.12,"livCen":0.12,"age18":0.15,"age35":0.09},{"text":"Waterloo Records","total":0.1,"yrs05":0.07,"yrs620":0.1,"yrs21":0.12,"livCou":0.09,"livAus":0.12,"livCen":0.14,"age18":0.07,"age35":0.12},{"text":"Formula One United States Grand Prix (at Circuit of the Americas)","total":0.1,"yrs05":0.08,"yrs620":0.12,"yrs21":0.09,"livCou":0.11,"livAus":0.08,"livCen":0.05,"age18":0.06,"age35":0.12},{"text":"Tito's Handmade Vodka","total":0.09,"yrs05":0.1,"yrs620":0.12,"yrs21":0.07,"livCou":0.09,"livAus":0.09,"livCen":0.13,"age18":0.09,"age35":0.09},{"text":"Threadgill's","total":0.08,"yrs05":0.04,"yrs620":0.06,"yrs21":0.11,"livCou":0.07,"livAus":0.09,"livCen":0.09,"age18":0.04,"age35":0.09},{"text":"BookPeople","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.07,"yrs620":0.06,"yrs21":0.07,"livCou":0.04,"livAus":0.1,"livCen":0.14,"age18":0.08,"age35":0.06},{"text":"Matt's El Rancho","total":0.06,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0.04,"yrs21":0.1,"livCou":0.06,"livAus":0.07,"livCen":0.08,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.09},{"text":"Republic of Texas Biker Rally","total":0.04,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0.02,"yrs21":0.06,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.05},{"text":"Schlotzsky's","total":0.04,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.05,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0.05,"age35":0.04},{"text":"Deep Eddy Vodka","total":0.03,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.04,"yrs21":0.03,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.05,"livCen":0.06,"age18":0.06,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Juan in a Million","total":0.03,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0.04,"yrs21":0.03,"livCou":0.03,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.04,"age35":0.02},{"text":"AMD (Advanced Micro Devices)","total":0.03,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.04,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.04},{"text":"Sweet Leaf Tea Company","total":0.03,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.03,"livCou":0.03,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.04,"age35":0.02},{"text":"El Arroyo","total":0.02,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.02,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Tacodeli","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.04,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.04,"age18":0.05,"age35":0.01},{"text":"McBride's Guns","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.03,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Austin Aztex","total":0.01,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.01},{"text":"Sup ATX","total":0.01,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0.02,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.01},{"text":"Love Puppies Brownies","total":0.01,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0.02,"age18":0.01,"age35":0},{"text":"LaRue Tactical","total":0,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0,"livCou":0,"livAus":0,"livCen":0,"age18":0,"age35":0},{"text":"Other","total":0,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0,"livCen":0,"age18":0.01,"age35":0}]},{"id":"Q37","note":null,"question":"Which one of the following do you consider the top thing Austin has gained due to its growth over the past five years?","answers":[{"text":"Stronger economy","total":0.42,"yrs05":0.37,"yrs620":0.51,"yrs21":0.37,"livCou":0.41,"livAus":0.42,"livCen":0.51,"age18":0.35,"age35":0.45},{"text":"More diversity","total":0.22,"yrs05":0.3,"yrs620":0.18,"yrs21":0.2,"livCou":0.2,"livAus":0.23,"livCen":0.21,"age18":0.27,"age35":0.19},{"text":"More creativity","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.1,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.07,"livCou":0.09,"livAus":0.04,"livCen":0.05,"age18":0.11,"age35":0.04},{"text":"Stronger sense of community","total":0.04,"yrs05":0.04,"yrs620":0.04,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.04,"livAus":0.04,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.06,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Mass transit","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.05,"yrs620":0.06,"yrs21":0.09,"livCou":0.06,"livAus":0.08,"livCen":0.04,"age18":0.08,"age35":0.06},{"text":"None of the above","total":0.19,"yrs05":0.14,"yrs620":0.18,"yrs21":0.23,"livCou":0.19,"livAus":0.2,"livCen":0.16,"age18":0.13,"age35":0.23}]},{"id":"Q38","note":null,"question":"Which one of the following do you consider the top thing Austin has lost due to its growth over the past five years?","answers":[{"text":"Lower cost of living","total":0.31,"yrs05":0.32,"yrs620":0.31,"yrs21":0.3,"livCou":0.26,"livAus":0.35,"livCen":0.37,"age18":0.37,"age35":0.27},{"text":"Ease of transportation","total":0.23,"yrs05":0.27,"yrs620":0.24,"yrs21":0.2,"livCou":0.29,"livAus":0.17,"livCen":0.19,"age18":0.21,"age35":0.24},{"text":"Less congested roads","total":0.23,"yrs05":0.26,"yrs620":0.27,"yrs21":0.19,"livCou":0.24,"livAus":0.21,"livCen":0.16,"age18":0.21,"age35":0.24},{"text":"Small town feel","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.09,"yrs620":0.1,"yrs21":0.18,"livCou":0.13,"livAus":0.15,"livCen":0.17,"age18":0.11,"age35":0.15},{"text":"Green space","total":0.03,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.03,"livAus":0.04,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.04,"age35":0.03},{"text":"Stable neighborhoods","total":0.03,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.03,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.04,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.03},{"text":"Historic homes throughout Austin","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0.03,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.02,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.02},{"text":"None of the above","total":0.03,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0.02,"yrs21":0.03,"livCou":0.03,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.02,"age18":0.03,"age35":0.02}]},{"id":"Q39","note":null,"question":"Which one of the following cities do you believe Austin is most similar to?","answers":[{"text":"Portland","total":0.21,"yrs05":0.25,"yrs620":0.25,"yrs21":0.16,"livCou":0.15,"livAus":0.27,"livCen":0.32,"age18":0.24,"age35":0.19},{"text":"Seattle","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.11,"yrs620":0.13,"yrs21":0.15,"livCou":0.16,"livAus":0.11,"livCen":0.13,"age18":0.09,"age35":0.16},{"text":"San Francisco","total":0.13,"yrs05":0.16,"yrs620":0.15,"yrs21":0.11,"livCou":0.14,"livAus":0.12,"livCen":0.1,"age18":0.15,"age35":0.12},{"text":"San Antonio","total":0.11,"yrs05":0.04,"yrs620":0.12,"yrs21":0.14,"livCou":0.12,"livAus":0.1,"livCen":0.06,"age18":0.14,"age35":0.09},{"text":"Dallas","total":0.1,"yrs05":0.06,"yrs620":0.09,"yrs21":0.12,"livCou":0.11,"livAus":0.09,"livCen":0.09,"age18":0.11,"age35":0.1},{"text":"Nashville","total":0.09,"yrs05":0.12,"yrs620":0.08,"yrs21":0.09,"livCou":0.1,"livAus":0.09,"livCen":0.1,"age18":0.06,"age35":0.11},{"text":"Houston","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.05,"yrs620":0.05,"yrs21":0.1,"livCou":0.09,"livAus":0.05,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.07,"age35":0.07},{"text":"Raleigh","total":0.03,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.02,"yrs21":0.03,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.03},{"text":"Boston","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.03,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.03},{"text":"New York City","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.05,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.04,"age35":0},{"text":"Washington, D.C.","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.02,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Other","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.07,"yrs620":0.06,"yrs21":0.08,"livCou":0.06,"livAus":0.08,"livCen":0.09,"age18":0.06,"age35":0.08}]},{"id":"Q40","note":null,"question":"If you had to move somewhere else in Texas, which one of the following cities/areas would you prefer to move to?","answers":[{"text":"San Antonio","total":0.27,"yrs05":0.34,"yrs620":0.24,"yrs21":0.27,"livCou":0.27,"livAus":0.28,"livCen":0.26,"age18":0.33,"age35":0.24},{"text":"Further away from Austin","total":0.23,"yrs05":0.15,"yrs620":0.19,"yrs21":0.28,"livCou":0.27,"livAus":0.18,"livCen":0.16,"age18":0.1,"age35":0.29},{"text":"Dallas/Ft. Worth","total":0.17,"yrs05":0.18,"yrs620":0.19,"yrs21":0.16,"livCou":0.15,"livAus":0.19,"livCen":0.2,"age18":0.23,"age35":0.14},{"text":"Houston","total":0.1,"yrs05":0.13,"yrs620":0.15,"yrs21":0.07,"livCou":0.08,"livAus":0.13,"livCen":0.16,"age18":0.15,"age35":0.08},{"text":"El Paso","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Other","total":0.2,"yrs05":0.18,"yrs620":0.2,"yrs21":0.22,"livCou":0.21,"livAus":0.2,"livCen":0.2,"age18":0.17,"age35":0.22}]},{"id":"Q41","note":null,"question":"Is Austin more a town of the past, present or future?","answers":[{"text":"Past","total":0.08,"yrs05":0.09,"yrs620":0.08,"yrs21":0.09,"livCou":0.08,"livAus":0.09,"livCen":0.05,"age18":0.07,"age35":0.09},{"text":"Present","total":0.41,"yrs05":0.45,"yrs620":0.42,"yrs21":0.39,"livCou":0.41,"livAus":0.41,"livCen":0.48,"age18":0.45,"age35":0.39},{"text":"Future","total":0.37,"yrs05":0.38,"yrs620":0.35,"yrs21":0.37,"livCou":0.36,"livAus":0.37,"livCen":0.31,"age18":0.36,"age35":0.37},{"text":"Unknown","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.08,"yrs620":0.14,"yrs21":0.16,"livCou":0.14,"livAus":0.13,"livCen":0.15,"age18":0.12,"age35":0.15}]},{"id":"Q42","note":null,"question":"If you were in charge of Austin, what would your main plan for the city be?","answers":[{"text":"Build for the future","total":0.58,"yrs05":0.59,"yrs620":0.67,"yrs21":0.52,"livCou":0.59,"livAus":0.57,"livCen":0.53,"age18":0.62,"age35":0.56},{"text":"Protect Austin as it is now","total":0.21,"yrs05":0.26,"yrs620":0.2,"yrs21":0.2,"livCou":0.21,"livAus":0.21,"livCen":0.27,"age18":0.2,"age35":0.22},{"text":"Return Austin to how it was in the past","total":0.21,"yrs05":0.15,"yrs620":0.13,"yrs21":0.28,"livCou":0.2,"livAus":0.22,"livCen":0.2,"age18":0.18,"age35":0.22}]},{"id":"Q43","note":null,"question":"What slogan best represents the Austin of today?","answers":[{"text":"\"Keep Austin Weird\"","total":0.29,"yrs05":0.44,"yrs620":0.23,"yrs21":0.27,"livCou":0.27,"livAus":0.32,"livCen":0.28,"age18":0.37,"age35":0.26},{"text":"\"Live Music Capital of the World\"","total":0.26,"yrs05":0.22,"yrs620":0.27,"yrs21":0.28,"livCou":0.31,"livAus":0.21,"livCen":0.2,"age18":0.26,"age35":0.27},{"text":"There's no one slogan that best represents the Austin of today","total":0.22,"yrs05":0.16,"yrs620":0.26,"yrs21":0.23,"livCou":0.22,"livAus":0.23,"livCen":0.27,"age18":0.18,"age35":0.25},{"text":"\"Don't Dallas My Austin\"","total":0.1,"yrs05":0.07,"yrs620":0.1,"yrs21":0.1,"livCou":0.06,"livAus":0.14,"livCen":0.16,"age18":0.12,"age35":0.08},{"text":"\"Bat City\"","total":0.01,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0,"age18":0,"age35":0.01},{"text":"I don't know","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.08,"yrs620":0.07,"yrs21":0.07,"livCou":0.1,"livAus":0.05,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.04,"age35":0.09},{"text":"I have my own","total":0.04,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.06,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.04,"livAus":0.05,"livCen":0.06,"age18":0.03,"age35":0.05}]},{"id":"Q45","note":null,"question":"Which feature of other major cities would most benefit Austin?","answers":[{"text":"Major sports team","total":0.18,"yrs05":0.19,"yrs620":0.17,"yrs21":0.18,"livCou":0.22,"livAus":0.13,"livCen":0.12,"age18":0.18,"age35":0.18},{"text":"Major art and cultural institutions and museums","total":0.26,"yrs05":0.32,"yrs620":0.28,"yrs21":0.23,"livCou":0.22,"livAus":0.31,"livCen":0.32,"age18":0.31,"age35":0.24},{"text":"Both","total":0.33,"yrs05":0.3,"yrs620":0.33,"yrs21":0.34,"livCou":0.31,"livAus":0.34,"livCen":0.35,"age18":0.34,"age35":0.32},{"text":"Neither","total":0.23,"yrs05":0.19,"yrs620":0.22,"yrs21":0.25,"livCou":0.24,"livAus":0.21,"livCen":0.21,"age18":0.18,"age35":0.26}]},{"id":"Q46","note":null,"question":"Whose town is this anyway?","answers":[{"text":"A haven for Millennials (born 1980 or after)/ young person's town","total":0.74,"yrs05":0.82,"yrs620":0.73,"yrs21":0.72,"livCou":0.74,"livAus":0.74,"livCen":0.78,"age18":0.88,"age35":0.67},{"text":"A Gen X/Baby Boomer town (born before 1980)","total":0.26,"yrs05":0.18,"yrs620":0.27,"yrs21":0.28,"livCou":0.26,"livAus":0.26,"livCen":0.22,"age18":0.12,"age35":0.33},{"text":"University of Texas' town","total":0.75,"yrs05":0.8,"yrs620":0.76,"yrs21":0.73,"livCou":0.72,"livAus":0.78,"livCen":0.84,"age18":0.8,"age35":0.73},{"text":"Texas State Government's town","total":0.25,"yrs05":0.2,"yrs620":0.24,"yrs21":0.27,"livCou":0.28,"livAus":0.22,"livCen":0.16,"age18":0.2,"age35":0.27},{"text":"A town for families","total":0.31,"yrs05":0.33,"yrs620":0.23,"yrs21":0.36,"livCou":0.3,"livAus":0.33,"livCen":0.29,"age18":0.27,"age35":0.33},{"text":"A town for singles","total":0.69,"yrs05":0.67,"yrs620":0.77,"yrs21":0.64,"livCou":0.7,"livAus":0.67,"livCen":0.71,"age18":0.73,"age35":0.67}]},{"id":"Q47","note":null,"question":"Do you think Austin has enough green and/or open spaces?","answers":[{"text":"Definitely","total":0.21,"yrs05":0.24,"yrs620":0.25,"yrs21":0.16,"livCou":0.2,"livAus":0.21,"livCen":0.21,"age18":0.25,"age35":0.18},{"text":"Somewhat","total":0.51,"yrs05":0.55,"yrs620":0.5,"yrs21":0.49,"livCou":0.49,"livAus":0.52,"livCen":0.55,"age18":0.55,"age35":0.48},{"text":"Not really","total":0.24,"yrs05":0.15,"yrs620":0.21,"yrs21":0.31,"livCou":0.27,"livAus":0.21,"livCen":0.2,"age18":0.18,"age35":0.28},{"text":"Not at all","total":0.05,"yrs05":0.05,"yrs620":0.05,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.04,"livAus":0.05,"livCen":0.04,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.06}]},{"id":"Q48","note":null,"question":"How concerned are you that rapid development and new construction projects threaten Austin's green and/or open spaces?","answers":[{"text":"Very concerned","total":0.35,"yrs05":0.28,"yrs620":0.3,"yrs21":0.41,"livCou":0.33,"livAus":0.37,"livCen":0.4,"age18":0.31,"age35":0.37},{"text":"Somewhat concerned","total":0.43,"yrs05":0.45,"yrs620":0.45,"yrs21":0.4,"livCou":0.42,"livAus":0.43,"livCen":0.42,"age18":0.45,"age35":0.41},{"text":"Not very concerned","total":0.15,"yrs05":0.16,"yrs620":0.17,"yrs21":0.13,"livCou":0.17,"livAus":0.13,"livCen":0.1,"age18":0.15,"age35":0.15},{"text":"Not concerned at all","total":0.05,"yrs05":0.06,"yrs620":0.07,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0.06,"livCen":0.07,"age18":0.06,"age35":0.05},{"text":"Unsure","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.05,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0.04,"age35":0.01}]},{"id":"Q49","note":"Select up to three","question":"Which green and/or open spaces in and around Austin do you personally enjoy the most?","answers":[{"text":"Zilker Park","total":0.57,"yrs05":0.53,"yrs620":0.58,"yrs21":0.58,"livCou":0.53,"livAus":0.61,"livCen":0.63,"age18":0.63,"age35":0.54},{"text":"Lake Travis and the surrounding area","total":0.34,"yrs05":0.31,"yrs620":0.36,"yrs21":0.35,"livCou":0.39,"livAus":0.3,"livCen":0.22,"age18":0.31,"age35":0.36},{"text":"Your neighborhood park","total":0.27,"yrs05":0.24,"yrs620":0.29,"yrs21":0.27,"livCou":0.24,"livAus":0.3,"livCen":0.23,"age18":0.24,"age35":0.28},{"text":"Barton Creek Greenbelt","total":0.24,"yrs05":0.26,"yrs620":0.21,"yrs21":0.26,"livCou":0.19,"livAus":0.3,"livCen":0.35,"age18":0.35,"age35":0.19},{"text":"Ann and Roy Butler Hike-and-Bike Trail at Lady Bird Lake (aka Town Lake Trail)","total":0.22,"yrs05":0.17,"yrs620":0.24,"yrs21":0.24,"livCou":0.17,"livAus":0.28,"livCen":0.36,"age18":0.21,"age35":0.23},{"text":"The Boardwalk Trail at Lady Bird Lake","total":0.17,"yrs05":0.17,"yrs620":0.24,"yrs21":0.14,"livCou":0.16,"livAus":0.19,"livCen":0.25,"age18":0.18,"age35":0.17},{"text":"Shoal Creek","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.07,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.09,"livCou":0.04,"livAus":0.09,"livCen":0.11,"age18":0.06,"age35":0.07},{"text":"Colorado River Wildlife Sanctuary","total":0.05,"yrs05":0.07,"yrs620":0.04,"yrs21":0.06,"livCou":0.06,"livAus":0.05,"livCen":0.05,"age18":0.07,"age35":0.05},{"text":"Waller Creek Greenbelt","total":0.03,"yrs05":0.05,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.03,"livCou":0.03,"livAus":0.04,"livCen":0.05,"age18":0.07,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Butler Park","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.04,"age18":0.03,"age35":0.01},{"text":"Other","total":0.03,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.05,"livCen":0.05,"age18":0.03,"age35":0.03},{"text":"None","total":0.1,"yrs05":0.1,"yrs620":0.1,"yrs21":0.1,"livCou":0.14,"livAus":0.06,"livCen":0.05,"age18":0.06,"age35":0.12}]},{"id":"Q50","note":null,"question":"Do you believe that pets in Austin are in public spaces, such as restaurant patios, too much?","answers":[{"text":"Definitely","total":0.23,"yrs05":0.19,"yrs620":0.25,"yrs21":0.23,"livCou":0.29,"livAus":0.17,"livCen":0.19,"age18":0.13,"age35":0.28},{"text":"Somewhat","total":0.24,"yrs05":0.21,"yrs620":0.24,"yrs21":0.26,"livCou":0.25,"livAus":0.24,"livCen":0.28,"age18":0.22,"age35":0.26},{"text":"Not really","total":0.32,"yrs05":0.36,"yrs620":0.33,"yrs21":0.3,"livCou":0.31,"livAus":0.33,"livCen":0.29,"age18":0.38,"age35":0.29},{"text":"Not at all","total":0.2,"yrs05":0.23,"yrs620":0.19,"yrs21":0.2,"livCou":0.15,"livAus":0.26,"livCen":0.23,"age18":0.28,"age35":0.16}]},{"id":"Q51","note":null,"question":"In your life, with which group do you feel the strongest sense of community?","answers":[{"text":"People from your neighborhood","total":0.19,"yrs05":0.11,"yrs620":0.21,"yrs21":0.2,"livCou":0.23,"livAus":0.14,"livCen":0.15,"age18":0.14,"age35":0.21},{"text":"People from work","total":0.18,"yrs05":0.15,"yrs620":0.16,"yrs21":0.2,"livCou":0.18,"livAus":0.18,"livCen":0.14,"age18":0.19,"age35":0.17},{"text":"People you know through hobbies","total":0.13,"yrs05":0.22,"yrs620":0.14,"yrs21":0.09,"livCou":0.13,"livAus":0.14,"livCen":0.18,"age18":0.19,"age35":0.1},{"text":"People from your religious community","total":0.12,"yrs05":0.1,"yrs620":0.12,"yrs21":0.13,"livCou":0.13,"livAus":0.11,"livCen":0.04,"age18":0.1,"age35":0.14},{"text":"People from your city generally","total":0.11,"yrs05":0.11,"yrs620":0.12,"yrs21":0.1,"livCou":0.08,"livAus":0.13,"livCen":0.15,"age18":0.08,"age35":0.12},{"text":"People you know through school","total":0.1,"yrs05":0.14,"yrs620":0.07,"yrs21":0.1,"livCou":0.1,"livAus":0.11,"livCen":0.16,"age18":0.16,"age35":0.07},{"text":"People you know through non-work organizations","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.05,"yrs620":0.08,"yrs21":0.06,"livCou":0.06,"livAus":0.07,"livCen":0.06,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.09},{"text":"People from your ethnic background","total":0.06,"yrs05":0.07,"yrs620":0.07,"yrs21":0.06,"livCou":0.04,"livAus":0.08,"livCen":0.09,"age18":0.08,"age35":0.05},{"text":"Online communities","total":0.05,"yrs05":0.05,"yrs620":0.04,"yrs21":0.05,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0.04,"livCen":0.04,"age18":0.03,"age35":0.05}]},{"id":"Q52","note":null,"question":"In your opinion, how often do you take advantage of Austin's cultural offerings?","answers":[{"text":"Frequently","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.12,"yrs620":0.14,"yrs21":0.15,"livCou":0.1,"livAus":0.19,"livCen":0.23,"age18":0.19,"age35":0.12},{"text":"Sometimes","total":0.48,"yrs05":0.48,"yrs620":0.48,"yrs21":0.49,"livCou":0.45,"livAus":0.52,"livCen":0.5,"age18":0.46,"age35":0.5},{"text":"Rarely","total":0.31,"yrs05":0.33,"yrs620":0.34,"yrs21":0.29,"livCou":0.36,"livAus":0.26,"livCen":0.23,"age18":0.27,"age35":0.34},{"text":"Never","total":0.06,"yrs05":0.07,"yrs620":0.04,"yrs21":0.07,"livCou":0.09,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.05,"age18":0.08,"age35":0.05}]},{"id":"Q53","note":null,"question":"How often do you attend religious services?","answers":[{"text":"Weekly or more often","total":0.21,"yrs05":0.19,"yrs620":0.23,"yrs21":0.21,"livCou":0.27,"livAus":0.16,"livCen":0.13,"age18":0.17,"age35":0.24},{"text":"1-2 times per month","total":0.1,"yrs05":0.06,"yrs620":0.08,"yrs21":0.12,"livCou":0.09,"livAus":0.11,"livCen":0.09,"age18":0.1,"age35":0.09},{"text":"Every 1-2 months","total":0.06,"yrs05":0.06,"yrs620":0.05,"yrs21":0.06,"livCou":0.04,"livAus":0.08,"livCen":0.05,"age18":0.07,"age35":0.05},{"text":"A few times per year","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.15,"yrs620":0.13,"yrs21":0.14,"livCou":0.17,"livAus":0.11,"livCen":0.14,"age18":0.11,"age35":0.16},{"text":"Once a year or less","total":0.17,"yrs05":0.12,"yrs620":0.19,"yrs21":0.19,"livCou":0.18,"livAus":0.17,"livCen":0.18,"age18":0.12,"age35":0.2},{"text":"Don't know","total":0.03,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.03,"livCou":0.04,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.02,"age18":0.04,"age35":0.02},{"text":"I am not religious","total":0.29,"yrs05":0.39,"yrs620":0.3,"yrs21":0.24,"livCou":0.22,"livAus":0.36,"livCen":0.4,"age18":0.39,"age35":0.23}]},{"id":"Q54","note":"Reporting 6-10","question":"Please rate, on a scale from zero to ten, how well-suited Austin is as a place to live for the following groups.","answers":[{"text":"Young adults without children","total":0.88,"yrs05":0.92,"yrs620":0.91,"yrs21":0.85,"livCou":0.88,"livAus":0.89,"livCen":0.91,"age18":0.93,"age35":0.86},{"text":"LGBT (lesbian, gay, bisexual, and transgender)","total":0.82,"yrs05":0.83,"yrs620":0.83,"yrs21":0.82,"livCou":0.78,"livAus":0.86,"livCen":0.92,"age18":0.86,"age35":0.8},{"text":"Asian Americans","total":0.76,"yrs05":0.8,"yrs620":0.78,"yrs21":0.73,"livCou":0.74,"livAus":0.78,"livCen":0.76,"age18":0.78,"age35":0.75},{"text":"Young college graduates looking for work","total":0.75,"yrs05":0.81,"yrs620":0.77,"yrs21":0.72,"livCou":0.77,"livAus":0.74,"livCen":0.73,"age18":0.77,"age35":0.75},{"text":"Hispanics","total":0.72,"yrs05":0.78,"yrs620":0.71,"yrs21":0.69,"livCou":0.68,"livAus":0.76,"livCen":0.72,"age18":0.78,"age35":0.68},{"text":"Families with young children","total":0.7,"yrs05":0.7,"yrs620":0.74,"yrs21":0.68,"livCou":0.67,"livAus":0.74,"livCen":0.73,"age18":0.74,"age35":0.69},{"text":"The middle class","total":0.66,"yrs05":0.66,"yrs620":0.7,"yrs21":0.62,"livCou":0.65,"livAus":0.67,"livCen":0.69,"age18":0.77,"age35":0.6},{"text":"People over the age of 50","total":0.59,"yrs05":0.58,"yrs620":0.6,"yrs21":0.59,"livCou":0.58,"livAus":0.6,"livCen":0.62,"age18":0.58,"age35":0.59},{"text":"Single parents","total":0.58,"yrs05":0.56,"yrs620":0.6,"yrs21":0.58,"livCou":0.54,"livAus":0.62,"livCen":0.57,"age18":0.6,"age35":0.57},{"text":"African Americans","total":0.58,"yrs05":0.62,"yrs620":0.56,"yrs21":0.58,"livCou":0.61,"livAus":0.56,"livCen":0.5,"age18":0.64,"age35":0.55},{"text":"Immigrants","total":0.53,"yrs05":0.62,"yrs620":0.47,"yrs21":0.53,"livCou":0.53,"livAus":0.53,"livCen":0.54,"age18":0.57,"age35":0.51},{"text":"The poor","total":0.25,"yrs05":0.28,"yrs620":0.24,"yrs21":0.24,"livCou":0.25,"livAus":0.25,"livCen":0.25,"age18":0.27,"age35":0.24}]},{"id":"Q55","note":null,"question":"Do you follow any specific diet?","answers":[{"text":"No, I don't have a specific diet","total":0.79,"yrs05":0.76,"yrs620":0.79,"yrs21":0.81,"livCou":0.83,"livAus":0.75,"livCen":0.73,"age18":0.78,"age35":0.8},{"text":"Gluten","total":0.06,"yrs05":0.06,"yrs620":0.05,"yrs21":0.07,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0.07,"livCen":0.08,"age18":0.09,"age35":0.05},{"text":"Vegetarian","total":0.05,"yrs05":0.1,"yrs620":0.05,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.03,"livAus":0.08,"livCen":0.12,"age18":0.07,"age35":0.05},{"text":"Lactose Intolerant","total":0.05,"yrs05":0.04,"yrs620":0.06,"yrs21":0.06,"livCou":0.03,"livAus":0.07,"livCen":0.06,"age18":0.05,"age35":0.05},{"text":"Paleo","total":0.04,"yrs05":0.04,"yrs620":0.04,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.04,"livAus":0.04,"livCen":0.07,"age18":0.05,"age35":0.03},{"text":"Vegan","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.03,"age35":0.01},{"text":"Other special diet","total":0.05,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.06,"yrs21":0.06,"livCou":0.03,"livAus":0.08,"livCen":0.08,"age18":0.04,"age35":0.06}]},{"id":"Q56","note":"Reporting Extremely/Very Important, and excluding Don't Know","question":"How important do you think these organizations, events, and/or festivals are to Austin's identity?","answers":[{"text":"SXSW (South by Southwest)","total":0.86,"yrs05":0.92,"yrs620":0.87,"yrs21":0.83,"livCou":0.86,"livAus":0.87,"livCen":0.89,"age18":0.86,"age35":0.86},{"text":"Austin City Limits Music Festival","total":0.86,"yrs05":0.9,"yrs620":0.86,"yrs21":0.83,"livCou":0.84,"livAus":0.87,"livCen":0.89,"age18":0.88,"age35":0.84},{"text":"UT Football Games","total":0.8,"yrs05":0.84,"yrs620":0.81,"yrs21":0.79,"livCou":0.82,"livAus":0.79,"livCen":0.76,"age18":0.83,"age35":0.79},{"text":"ACL Live at The Moody Theater","total":0.72,"yrs05":0.79,"yrs620":0.75,"yrs21":0.67,"livCou":0.69,"livAus":0.75,"livCen":0.77,"age18":0.74,"age35":0.71},{"text":"Pecan Street Festival","total":0.63,"yrs05":0.59,"yrs620":0.6,"yrs21":0.66,"livCou":0.61,"livAus":0.65,"livCen":0.64,"age18":0.67,"age35":0.61},{"text":"Zilker Kite Festival","total":0.6,"yrs05":0.68,"yrs620":0.57,"yrs21":0.59,"livCou":0.59,"livAus":0.61,"livCen":0.63,"age18":0.73,"age35":0.53},{"text":"Formula One United States Grand Prix (at Circuit of the Americas)","total":0.57,"yrs05":0.6,"yrs620":0.61,"yrs21":0.54,"livCou":0.61,"livAus":0.54,"livCen":0.49,"age18":0.62,"age35":0.55},{"text":"Austin Food & Wine Festival","total":0.55,"yrs05":0.69,"yrs620":0.54,"yrs21":0.5,"livCou":0.56,"livAus":0.54,"livCen":0.53,"age18":0.67,"age35":0.49},{"text":"Blues on the Green","total":0.52,"yrs05":0.55,"yrs620":0.49,"yrs21":0.52,"livCou":0.48,"livAus":0.56,"livCen":0.63,"age18":0.65,"age35":0.45},{"text":"FUN FUN FUN FEST","total":0.48,"yrs05":0.61,"yrs620":0.45,"yrs21":0.45,"livCou":0.45,"livAus":0.51,"livCen":0.58,"age18":0.6,"age35":0.42},{"text":"The Texas Relays","total":0.48,"yrs05":0.47,"yrs620":0.44,"yrs21":0.5,"livCou":0.52,"livAus":0.43,"livCen":0.38,"age18":0.48,"age35":0.47},{"text":"Republic of Texas Biker Rally","total":0.45,"yrs05":0.48,"yrs620":0.43,"yrs21":0.45,"livCou":0.48,"livAus":0.42,"livCen":0.4,"age18":0.53,"age35":0.41},{"text":"X Games","total":0.44,"yrs05":0.48,"yrs620":0.44,"yrs21":0.43,"livCou":0.49,"livAus":0.39,"livCen":0.38,"age18":0.53,"age35":0.4},{"text":"Ballet Austin","total":0.44,"yrs05":0.39,"yrs620":0.39,"yrs21":0.49,"livCou":0.39,"livAus":0.49,"livCen":0.46,"age18":0.54,"age35":0.39},{"text":"Marley Fest/Austin Reggae Festival","total":0.44,"yrs05":0.53,"yrs620":0.42,"yrs21":0.42,"livCou":0.42,"livAus":0.45,"livCen":0.45,"age18":0.6,"age35":0.35},{"text":"Eeyore's Birthday Party","total":0.4,"yrs05":0.41,"yrs620":0.33,"yrs21":0.43,"livCou":0.33,"livAus":0.46,"livCen":0.52,"age18":0.49,"age35":0.35},{"text":"Austin Startup Week","total":0.39,"yrs05":0.61,"yrs620":0.37,"yrs21":0.32,"livCou":0.36,"livAus":0.43,"livCen":0.44,"age18":0.6,"age35":0.28},{"text":"Austin Lyric Opera","total":0.37,"yrs05":0.4,"yrs620":0.32,"yrs21":0.39,"livCou":0.37,"livAus":0.37,"livCen":0.31,"age18":0.45,"age35":0.33},{"text":"African American Community Heritage Festival (AACHF)","total":0.35,"yrs05":0.47,"yrs620":0.32,"yrs21":0.33,"livCou":0.33,"livAus":0.38,"livCen":0.39,"age18":0.48,"age35":0.29},{"text":"Brazilian Carnival","total":0.25,"yrs05":0.4,"yrs620":0.23,"yrs21":0.21,"livCou":0.24,"livAus":0.26,"livCen":0.27,"age18":0.38,"age35":0.18},{"text":"Fusebox Festival","total":0.25,"yrs05":0.34,"yrs620":0.21,"yrs21":0.24,"livCou":0.28,"livAus":0.22,"livCen":0.21,"age18":0.38,"age35":0.18}]},{"id":"Q57","note":"Reporting Extremely/Very Important, and excluding Don't Know","question":"How important are these organizations, events, and/or festivals are to you personally?","answers":[{"text":"Austin City Limits Music Festival","total":0.42,"yrs05":0.42,"yrs620":0.43,"yrs21":0.41,"livCou":0.36,"livAus":0.49,"livCen":0.59,"age18":0.52,"age35":0.37},{"text":"SXSW (South by Southwest)","total":0.4,"yrs05":0.46,"yrs620":0.39,"yrs21":0.37,"livCou":0.36,"livAus":0.44,"livCen":0.52,"age18":0.52,"age35":0.33},{"text":"UT Football Games","total":0.38,"yrs05":0.33,"yrs620":0.37,"yrs21":0.41,"livCou":0.38,"livAus":0.39,"livCen":0.43,"age18":0.42,"age35":0.36},{"text":"Pecan Street Festival","total":0.34,"yrs05":0.25,"yrs620":0.3,"yrs21":0.4,"livCou":0.33,"livAus":0.35,"livCen":0.36,"age18":0.36,"age35":0.33},{"text":"ACL Live at The Moody Theater","total":0.32,"yrs05":0.34,"yrs620":0.35,"yrs21":0.3,"livCou":0.27,"livAus":0.38,"livCen":0.43,"age18":0.35,"age35":0.31},{"text":"Zilker Kite Festival","total":0.28,"yrs05":0.28,"yrs620":0.27,"yrs21":0.28,"livCou":0.24,"livAus":0.32,"livCen":0.31,"age18":0.37,"age35":0.24},{"text":"Blues on the Green","total":0.26,"yrs05":0.27,"yrs620":0.26,"yrs21":0.26,"livCou":0.21,"livAus":0.32,"livCen":0.38,"age18":0.38,"age35":0.2},{"text":"Austin Food & Wine Festival","total":0.25,"yrs05":0.31,"yrs620":0.23,"yrs21":0.24,"livCou":0.23,"livAus":0.26,"livCen":0.23,"age18":0.34,"age35":0.2},{"text":"FUN FUN FUN FEST","total":0.23,"yrs05":0.32,"yrs620":0.2,"yrs21":0.21,"livCou":0.2,"livAus":0.26,"livCen":0.3,"age18":0.32,"age35":0.18},{"text":"Formula One United States Grand Prix (at Circuit of the Americas)","total":0.22,"yrs05":0.25,"yrs620":0.2,"yrs21":0.23,"livCou":0.23,"livAus":0.22,"livCen":0.23,"age18":0.27,"age35":0.2},{"text":"Eeyore's Birthday Party","total":0.19,"yrs05":0.19,"yrs620":0.13,"yrs21":0.22,"livCou":0.13,"livAus":0.24,"livCen":0.25,"age18":0.22,"age35":0.17},{"text":"Ballet Austin","total":0.18,"yrs05":0.17,"yrs620":0.18,"yrs21":0.19,"livCou":0.15,"livAus":0.21,"livCen":0.2,"age18":0.22,"age35":0.16},{"text":"Marley Fest/Austin Reggae Festival","total":0.18,"yrs05":0.2,"yrs620":0.16,"yrs21":0.18,"livCou":0.16,"livAus":0.2,"livCen":0.2,"age18":0.27,"age35":0.13},{"text":"The Texas Relays","total":0.16,"yrs05":0.16,"yrs620":0.14,"yrs21":0.18,"livCou":0.17,"livAus":0.16,"livCen":0.15,"age18":0.22,"age35":0.14},{"text":"X Games","total":0.15,"yrs05":0.18,"yrs620":0.15,"yrs21":0.14,"livCou":0.15,"livAus":0.15,"livCen":0.11,"age18":0.24,"age35":0.11},{"text":"Republic of Texas Biker Rally","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.12,"yrs620":0.13,"yrs21":0.16,"livCou":0.16,"livAus":0.13,"livCen":0.11,"age18":0.17,"age35":0.13},{"text":"African American Community Heritage Festival (AACHF)","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.15,"yrs620":0.14,"yrs21":0.13,"livCou":0.12,"livAus":0.15,"livCen":0.15,"age18":0.22,"age35":0.09},{"text":"Austin Startup Week","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.17,"yrs620":0.13,"yrs21":0.12,"livCou":0.14,"livAus":0.13,"livCen":0.16,"age18":0.24,"age35":0.08},{"text":"Austin Lyric Opera","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.12,"yrs620":0.13,"yrs21":0.14,"livCou":0.12,"livAus":0.15,"livCen":0.14,"age18":0.17,"age35":0.12},{"text":"Brazilian Carnival","total":0.11,"yrs05":0.09,"yrs620":0.11,"yrs21":0.11,"livCou":0.09,"livAus":0.12,"livCen":0.12,"age18":0.17,"age35":0.08},{"text":"Fusebox Festival","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.09,"yrs620":0.08,"yrs21":0.06,"livCou":0.08,"livAus":0.07,"livCen":0.08,"age18":0.13,"age35":0.05}]},{"id":"Q58","note":null,"question":"Which two of the following events would you most support Austin hosting?","answers":[{"text":"Summer Olympic Games","total":0.31,"yrs05":0.33,"yrs620":0.29,"yrs21":0.32,"livCou":0.33,"livAus":0.3,"livCen":0.26,"age18":0.36,"age35":0.28},{"text":"Super Bowl","total":0.3,"yrs05":0.29,"yrs620":0.27,"yrs21":0.32,"livCou":0.33,"livAus":0.26,"livCen":0.2,"age18":0.34,"age35":0.27},{"text":"Presidential Debate","total":0.22,"yrs05":0.23,"yrs620":0.24,"yrs21":0.21,"livCou":0.18,"livAus":0.27,"livCen":0.31,"age18":0.21,"age35":0.23},{"text":"Democratic or Republican National Convention","total":0.19,"yrs05":0.13,"yrs620":0.24,"yrs21":0.18,"livCou":0.16,"livAus":0.22,"livCen":0.26,"age18":0.16,"age35":0.2},{"text":"Soccer World Cup","total":0.17,"yrs05":0.2,"yrs620":0.2,"yrs21":0.14,"livCou":0.12,"livAus":0.23,"livCen":0.24,"age18":0.22,"age35":0.15},{"text":"Major Professional Golf Association (PGA) tournament","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.09,"yrs620":0.17,"yrs21":0.14,"livCou":0.17,"livAus":0.1,"livCen":0.11,"age18":0.08,"age35":0.17},{"text":"Miss America/Miss Universe","total":0.08,"yrs05":0.12,"yrs620":0.06,"yrs21":0.08,"livCou":0.09,"livAus":0.07,"livCen":0.07,"age18":0.11,"age35":0.06},{"text":"Other","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.04,"yrs620":0.02,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.02},{"text":"None of the above","total":0.19,"yrs05":0.17,"yrs620":0.18,"yrs21":0.2,"livCou":0.2,"livAus":0.18,"livCen":0.16,"age18":0.16,"age35":0.21}]},{"id":"Q59","note":"Select up to three","question":"Why would you not want Austin to host those major events?","answers":[{"text":"Traffic congestion","total":0.71,"yrs05":0.61,"yrs620":0.74,"yrs21":0.74,"livCou":0.78,"livAus":0.63,"livCen":0.6,"age18":0.59,"age35":0.76},{"text":"Too expensive","total":0.35,"yrs05":0.44,"yrs620":0.34,"yrs21":0.31,"livCou":0.34,"livAus":0.35,"livCen":0.32,"age18":0.35,"age35":0.35},{"text":"Lacking infrastructure","total":0.31,"yrs05":0.22,"yrs620":0.35,"yrs21":0.32,"livCou":0.26,"livAus":0.36,"livCen":0.38,"age18":0.15,"age35":0.37},{"text":"Would not benefit me","total":0.28,"yrs05":0.22,"yrs620":0.3,"yrs21":0.28,"livCou":0.29,"livAus":0.26,"livCen":0.23,"age18":0.32,"age35":0.26},{"text":"Austin should pull back from the \"big events\" business","total":0.16,"yrs05":0.1,"yrs620":0.16,"yrs21":0.17,"livCou":0.14,"livAus":0.18,"livCen":0.23,"age18":0.11,"age35":0.17},{"text":"Too corporate","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.11,"yrs620":0.18,"yrs21":0.12,"livCou":0.11,"livAus":0.16,"livCen":0.21,"age18":0.15,"age35":0.13},{"text":"Too political","total":0.13,"yrs05":0.08,"yrs620":0.25,"yrs21":0.09,"livCou":0.17,"livAus":0.09,"livCen":0.08,"age18":0.15,"age35":0.13},{"text":"Don't want Austin to lose its \"weird\" factor","total":0.08,"yrs05":0.1,"yrs620":0.04,"yrs21":0.08,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0.11,"livCen":0.19,"age18":0.12,"age35":0.06},{"text":"Other","total":0.02,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0.05,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.07,"age18":0,"age35":0.03}]},{"id":"Q60","note":"Reporting Extremely/Very Satisfied","question":"How satisfied are you with the following creative offerings in Austin?","answers":[{"text":"Festivals (e.g., South by Southwest, ACL Music Festival, Austin Chamber Music Festival, FUN FUN FUN FEST)","total":0.67,"yrs05":0.75,"yrs620":0.7,"yrs21":0.61,"livCou":0.64,"livAus":0.69,"livCen":0.8,"age18":0.77,"age35":0.61},{"text":"Free Concerts (e.g., Blues on the Green, Texas Radio Live)","total":0.63,"yrs05":0.7,"yrs620":0.6,"yrs21":0.62,"livCou":0.59,"livAus":0.67,"livCen":0.76,"age18":0.73,"age35":0.58},{"text":"Museums (e.g., Blanton Museum of Art, Mexic","total":0.6,"yrs05":0.64,"yrs620":0.53,"yrs21":0.63,"livCou":0.58,"livAus":0.62,"livCen":0.65,"age18":0.62,"age35":0.59},{"text":"Performing Arts (e.g., Ballet Austin, ZACH Theatre)","total":0.57,"yrs05":0.58,"yrs620":0.51,"yrs21":0.6,"livCou":0.52,"livAus":0.61,"livCen":0.64,"age18":0.65,"age35":0.52},{"text":"Comedy Shows (e.g., Esther's Follies, Cap City Comedy Club, Moontower Comedy Festival)","total":0.53,"yrs05":0.58,"yrs620":0.53,"yrs21":0.51,"livCou":0.54,"livAus":0.52,"livCen":0.59,"age18":0.62,"age35":0.48},{"text":"Art (e.g., The East Austin Handmade Arts Market, Art City Austin, East Austin Studio Tour)","total":0.5,"yrs05":0.59,"yrs620":0.46,"yrs21":0.48,"livCou":0.43,"livAus":0.56,"livCen":0.6,"age18":0.61,"age35":0.43},{"text":"Creative camps/classes geared toward children","total":0.49,"yrs05":0.51,"yrs620":0.51,"yrs21":0.48,"livCou":0.47,"livAus":0.52,"livCen":0.56,"age18":0.55,"age35":0.46}]},{"id":"Q61","note":null,"question":"Which of the following statements best characterizes your feelings about Austin's creative culture?","answers":[{"text":"The creative culture in Austin is what makes this a great city to live in","total":0.41,"yrs05":0.51,"yrs620":0.4,"yrs21":0.37,"livCou":0.38,"livAus":0.44,"livCen":0.48,"age18":0.51,"age35":0.35},{"text":"The creative culture in Austin has been pushed out by a booming population and changing economy","total":0.26,"yrs05":0.15,"yrs620":0.23,"yrs21":0.32,"livCou":0.21,"livAus":0.31,"livCen":0.35,"age18":0.23,"age35":0.28},{"text":"The creative culture in Austin has a minimal impact on my life","total":0.21,"yrs05":0.19,"yrs620":0.26,"yrs21":0.2,"livCou":0.26,"livAus":0.17,"livCen":0.12,"age18":0.13,"age35":0.26},{"text":"I don't care about the creative culture in Austin","total":0.06,"yrs05":0.07,"yrs620":0.05,"yrs21":0.07,"livCou":0.09,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.02,"age18":0.05,"age35":0.07},{"text":"Don't know","total":0.06,"yrs05":0.08,"yrs620":0.07,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.06,"livAus":0.05,"livCen":0.04,"age18":0.08,"age35":0.04}]},{"id":"Q62","note":null,"question":"How many tattoos do you have?","answers":[{"text":"0","total":0.71,"yrs05":0.67,"yrs620":0.71,"yrs21":0.72,"livCou":0.72,"livAus":0.69,"livCen":0.68,"age18":0.63,"age35":0.74},{"text":"1","total":0.08,"yrs05":0.09,"yrs620":0.08,"yrs21":0.08,"livCou":0.07,"livAus":0.1,"livCen":0.09,"age18":0.11,"age35":0.07},{"text":"2","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.1,"yrs620":0.06,"yrs21":0.07,"livCou":0.08,"livAus":0.06,"livCen":0.06,"age18":0.08,"age35":0.07},{"text":"3","total":0.04,"yrs05":0.05,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.03,"livAus":0.05,"livCen":0.06,"age18":0.07,"age35":0.03},{"text":"4","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0.02,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0.03,"age35":0.02},{"text":"5 or more","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.07,"yrs620":0.09,"yrs21":0.06,"livCou":0.07,"livAus":0.08,"livCen":0.08,"age18":0.08,"age35":0.07},{"text":"Prefer not to answer","total":0.01,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0,"livCou":0,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0,"age35":0.01}]},{"id":"D1","note":null,"question":"Were you raised in the Austin area?","answers":[{"text":"Yes","total":0.29,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0.59,"livCou":0.25,"livAus":0.32,"livCen":0.29,"age18":0.38,"age35":0.24},{"text":"No","total":0.71,"yrs05":1,"yrs620":1,"yrs21":0.41,"livCou":0.75,"livAus":0.68,"livCen":0.71,"age18":0.62,"age35":0.76}]},{"id":"D2","note":"Reported as number of years in Austin netted, including the life span of those raised in Austin.","question":"In what year did you move to the Austin area?","answers":[{"text":"0-5 years","total":0.21,"yrs05":1,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0,"livCou":0.2,"livAus":0.23,"livCen":0.28,"age18":0.35,"age35":0.14},{"text":"6-20 years","total":0.3,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":1,"yrs21":0,"livCou":0.32,"livAus":0.28,"livCen":0.27,"age18":0.26,"age35":0.33},{"text":"21+ years","total":0.49,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":1,"livCou":0.48,"livAus":0.49,"livCen":0.45,"age18":0.39,"age35":0.54}]},{"id":"D3","note":null,"question":"What is the last grade of school you completed?","answers":[{"text":"High school grad or less","total":0.16,"yrs05":0.06,"yrs620":0.16,"yrs21":0.2,"livCou":0.21,"livAus":0.11,"livCen":0.08,"age18":0.18,"age35":0.15},{"text":"Some college","total":0.43,"yrs05":0.52,"yrs620":0.31,"yrs21":0.47,"livCou":0.45,"livAus":0.41,"livCen":0.45,"age18":0.47,"age35":0.41},{"text":"College+","total":0.41,"yrs05":0.41,"yrs620":0.53,"yrs21":0.33,"livCou":0.34,"livAus":0.48,"livCen":0.45,"age18":0.35,"age35":0.44},{"text":"Prefer not to answer","total":0,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0,"livCou":0,"livAus":0,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0.01,"age35":0}]},{"id":"D4","note":null,"question":"Which of the following best describes your current employment status?","answers":[{"text":"Employed full time","total":0.48,"yrs05":0.35,"yrs620":0.59,"yrs21":0.46,"livCou":0.38,"livAus":0.58,"livCen":0.53,"age18":0.48,"age35":0.47},{"text":"Employed part time","total":0.1,"yrs05":0.15,"yrs620":0.1,"yrs21":0.09,"livCou":0.1,"livAus":0.11,"livCen":0.11,"age18":0.16,"age35":0.08},{"text":"Under-employed given my skills, but working full time","total":0.01,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.01},{"text":"Under-employed given my skills, working part time","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.04,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.02,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Full-time homemaker","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.09,"yrs620":0.06,"yrs21":0.07,"livCou":0.1,"livAus":0.04,"livCen":0.05,"age18":0.1,"age35":0.06},{"text":"Student","total":0.06,"yrs05":0.15,"yrs620":0.02,"yrs21":0.05,"livCou":0.06,"livAus":0.07,"livCen":0.09,"age18":0.15,"age35":0.01},{"text":"Retired","total":0.16,"yrs05":0.1,"yrs620":0.14,"yrs21":0.2,"livCou":0.24,"livAus":0.08,"livCen":0.07,"age18":0,"age35":0.25},{"text":"Unemployed","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.08,"yrs620":0.05,"yrs21":0.09,"livCou":0.07,"livAus":0.08,"livCen":0.08,"age18":0.08,"age35":0.07},{"text":"Other","total":0.03,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.03,"livCou":0.03,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.04,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.04}]},{"id":"D5","note":null,"question":"In which sector have you primarily worked over the course of your career?","answers":[{"text":"Technology","total":0.14,"yrs05":0.12,"yrs620":0.17,"yrs21":0.13,"livCou":0.15,"livAus":0.13,"livCen":0.12,"age18":0.1,"age35":0.16},{"text":"Education","total":0.13,"yrs05":0.15,"yrs620":0.13,"yrs21":0.13,"livCou":0.15,"livAus":0.13,"livCen":0.13,"age18":0.16,"age35":0.12},{"text":"Service industry (hotels, retail, restaurants, bars)","total":0.11,"yrs05":0.18,"yrs620":0.1,"yrs21":0.1,"livCou":0.1,"livAus":0.12,"livCen":0.17,"age18":0.23,"age35":0.04},{"text":"Federal, state or local government","total":0.1,"yrs05":0.09,"yrs620":0.12,"yrs21":0.09,"livCou":0.13,"livAus":0.08,"livCen":0.07,"age18":0.04,"age35":0.14},{"text":"Healthcare/Medicine","total":0.09,"yrs05":0.14,"yrs620":0.07,"yrs21":0.09,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0.12,"livCen":0.15,"age18":0.09,"age35":0.1},{"text":"Accounting and Finance","total":0.05,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.02,"yrs21":0.08,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0.05,"livCen":0.05,"age18":0.04,"age35":0.05},{"text":"Real estate","total":0.03,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.02,"yrs21":0.03,"livCou":0.03,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0.05,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Creative (design, fashion, art, music, writing)","total":0.03,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.03,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.07,"age18":0.04,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Law/Legal Services","total":0.03,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.02,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.03},{"text":"Transportation","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0.03,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.03,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Consulting","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0.02,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.03,"age18":0,"age35":0.03},{"text":"Entrepreneurial/Business Owner","total":0.01,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Communications","total":0.01,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.01},{"text":"Energy or Utilities","total":0.01,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0.02,"yrs21":0,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Entertainment/Festivals","total":0.01,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0.02,"age18":0,"age35":0.01},{"text":"Farming or Agriculture","total":0.01,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.02,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.01},{"text":"Public Relations/Public Affairs","total":0,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0,"livCen":0,"age18":0,"age35":0.01},{"text":"None of these","total":0.19,"yrs05":0.14,"yrs620":0.23,"yrs21":0.17,"livCou":0.25,"livAus":0.14,"livCen":0.09,"age18":0.19,"age35":0.18}]},{"id":"D6","note":null,"question":"Have you voted in the last 4 years?","answers":[{"text":"Yes","total":0.73,"yrs05":0.57,"yrs620":0.81,"yrs21":0.74,"livCou":0.71,"livAus":0.75,"livCen":0.75,"age18":0.52,"age35":0.84},{"text":"No","total":0.27,"yrs05":0.42,"yrs620":0.19,"yrs21":0.24,"livCou":0.28,"livAus":0.25,"livCen":0.24,"age18":0.48,"age35":0.15},{"text":"Don't know","total":0.01,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.01}]},{"id":"D7","note":null,"question":"Generally speaking, which of the following best describes your political party affiliation?","answers":[{"text":"Democrat","total":0.45,"yrs05":0.38,"yrs620":0.46,"yrs21":0.47,"livCou":0.33,"livAus":0.57,"livCen":0.63,"age18":0.41,"age35":0.47},{"text":"Republican","total":0.29,"yrs05":0.33,"yrs620":0.32,"yrs21":0.25,"livCou":0.38,"livAus":0.2,"livCen":0.15,"age18":0.26,"age35":0.31},{"text":"Independent","total":0.08,"yrs05":0.05,"yrs620":0.09,"yrs21":0.08,"livCou":0.08,"livAus":0.07,"livCen":0.05,"age18":0.05,"age35":0.09},{"text":"Other/Don't know/ Prefer not to answer","total":0.19,"yrs05":0.23,"yrs620":0.13,"yrs21":0.21,"livCou":0.21,"livAus":0.16,"livCen":0.16,"age18":0.29,"age35":0.14}]},{"id":"D8","note":null,"question":"Did you or do you attend any of the following universities or colleges located in Austin?","answers":[{"text":"Austin Community College","total":0.24,"yrs05":0.08,"yrs620":0.14,"yrs21":0.36,"livCou":0.19,"livAus":0.29,"livCen":0.29,"age18":0.25,"age35":0.23},{"text":"The University of Texas at Austin","total":0.16,"yrs05":0.13,"yrs620":0.12,"yrs21":0.21,"livCou":0.1,"livAus":0.23,"livCen":0.26,"age18":0.17,"age35":0.16},{"text":"St. Edwards University","total":0.03,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0.02,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.04,"livCen":0.04,"age18":0.03,"age35":0.03},{"text":"Concordia University Texas","total":0.02,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.03,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0.02,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0.02,"age35":0.02},{"text":"Acton School of Business (Hardin-Simmons University)","total":0.01,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0,"livCen":0,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.01},{"text":"Huston-Tillotson University","total":0.01,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0,"age18":0,"age35":0.01},{"text":"Texas Health and Science University","total":0.01,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0,"yrs21":0.01,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0,"livCen":0,"age18":0,"age35":0.01},{"text":"None of the above","total":0.62,"yrs05":0.79,"yrs620":0.74,"yrs21":0.46,"livCou":0.7,"livAus":0.52,"livCen":0.46,"age18":0.57,"age35":0.64}]},{"id":"D9","note":null,"question":"Which of the following best describes your marital status?","answers":[{"text":"Married","total":0.48,"yrs05":0.41,"yrs620":0.54,"yrs21":0.48,"livCou":0.6,"livAus":0.36,"livCen":0.26,"age18":0.25,"age35":0.61},{"text":"Single, never married","total":0.29,"yrs05":0.35,"yrs620":0.26,"yrs21":0.29,"livCou":0.2,"livAus":0.39,"livCen":0.52,"age18":0.52,"age35":0.17},{"text":"Single and living with a partner","total":0.11,"yrs05":0.17,"yrs620":0.07,"yrs21":0.11,"livCou":0.08,"livAus":0.14,"livCen":0.13,"age18":0.2,"age35":0.06},{"text":"Divorced","total":0.07,"yrs05":0.04,"yrs620":0.07,"yrs21":0.09,"livCou":0.06,"livAus":0.08,"livCen":0.07,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.11},{"text":"Widowed","total":0.03,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0.05,"yrs21":0.03,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0,"age35":0.04},{"text":"Separated","total":0.01,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0,"livCou":0,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.01},{"text":"Prefer not to answer","total":0.01,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0,"livCen":0,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.01}]},{"id":"D10","note":null,"question":"Do you own or rent your current place of residence?","answers":[{"text":"Own","total":0.57,"yrs05":0.29,"yrs620":0.63,"yrs21":0.65,"livCou":0.68,"livAus":0.45,"livCen":0.37,"age18":0.27,"age35":0.73},{"text":"Rent","total":0.41,"yrs05":0.68,"yrs620":0.35,"yrs21":0.33,"livCou":0.3,"livAus":0.53,"livCen":0.62,"age18":0.68,"age35":0.27},{"text":"Don't know","total":0.01,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0.02,"livCou":0.02,"livAus":0,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0.03,"age35":0},{"text":"Prefer not to answer","total":0.01,"yrs05":0.02,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0,"livCou":0.01,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0.02,"age35":0}]},{"id":"D1112","note":null,"question":"How many languages, besides English or Spanish, are spoken in your home on a daily basis?","answers":[{"text":"None, just English/Spanish","total":0.73,"yrs05":0.7,"yrs620":0.73,"yrs21":0.75,"livCou":0.72,"livAus":0.74,"livCen":0.75,"age18":0.68,"age35":0.76},{"text":"1","total":0.2,"yrs05":0.19,"yrs620":0.2,"yrs21":0.21,"livCou":0.21,"livAus":0.2,"livCen":0.19,"age18":0.23,"age35":0.19},{"text":"2","total":0.06,"yrs05":0.1,"yrs620":0.06,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.07,"livAus":0.05,"livCen":0.05,"age18":0.08,"age35":0.05},{"text":"3 or more","total":0.01,"yrs05":0.01,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0,"livCou":0,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.01}]},{"id":"D13","note":null,"question":"Through which method do you get the majority of your news?","answers":[{"text":"Online","total":0.45,"yrs05":0.54,"yrs620":0.49,"yrs21":0.39,"livCou":0.4,"livAus":0.51,"livCen":0.55,"age18":0.57,"age35":0.39},{"text":"TV","total":0.4,"yrs05":0.29,"yrs620":0.35,"yrs21":0.48,"livCou":0.47,"livAus":0.33,"livCen":0.27,"age18":0.29,"age35":0.46},{"text":"Radio","total":0.05,"yrs05":0.08,"yrs620":0.05,"yrs21":0.04,"livCou":0.04,"livAus":0.06,"livCen":0.06,"age18":0.07,"age35":0.04},{"text":"Print","total":0.05,"yrs05":0.03,"yrs620":0.05,"yrs21":0.06,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0.05,"livCen":0.07,"age18":0.01,"age35":0.07},{"text":"I don't keep up with news","total":0.04,"yrs05":0.07,"yrs620":0.05,"yrs21":0.03,"livCou":0.05,"livAus":0.04,"livCen":0.05,"age18":0.07,"age35":0.03},{"text":"Other","total":0,"yrs05":0,"yrs620":0.01,"yrs21":0,"livCou":0,"livAus":0.01,"livCen":0.01,"age18":0,"age35":0.01}]}]